(This show features indirect advertisements.)
(Running Man)
Come on in.
(One scorching hot summer day)
- Okay. - Hello.
(One coffee shop in Jeongdong-gil)
- Hello. - All right.
All right. Okay.
You are wearing all those days on your chest all week?
"Leg?"
- It says "Leg day." - Yes.
(Today is leg day.)
What is a leg day?
It's an important day.
(Following Trainer Kook with his unyielding fashion commitment)
- Ji Hyo, you look... - Ji Hyo...
- Are you a goddess or what? - It looks like...
- you're at an awards ceremony. - Are you getting a tan?
(Ji Hyo's extreme off-shoulder look)
- Because it's hot? - It's hot.
- I see. - Where's your claw clip?
(Her signature)
Where did you put your claw clip?
(Goodbye to Ji Hyo's favorite claw clip)
- That darn claw clip. - Seriously, my claw clip...
I'm seeing Ji Hyo's bare shoulders after a long time.
Your shoulders have gotten really rounded.
(Cool)
We saw Ji Hyo's belly the other day.
- It's extreme. - Yes.
- It's all or nothing. - It's all or nothing.
(Revealing her bare shoulders after her bare stomach)
- Yes. - Song Ji Hyo.
We have guests...
(Today's guests are as extreme as Ji Hyo's fashion.)
- for today. - Do we have guests?
Please bring the guests in.
- Who are they? - Who?
- Hello! - Hello.
(Loud)
(Comedienne and variety show trendsetter, Kim Ji Yu)
- Hello. - Hey.
- Hello. - You're here.
(Running Man's family member, Hong Jin Ho)
- Please stand in the middle. - Hello.
(It was famous for its double-faced wool suits.)
It was famous for its double-faced wool suits...
Wool socks.
(An expert in the undecipherable Jin Ho's language)
- Body language. What is this? - This is difficult.
Why are you stealing from us? You should steal from them.
Why are you stealing from your own team?
(Dubbed by Jin Ho himself)
(Pronunciation Genius Kong Jin Ho)
You should steal from the other team.
I was like this.
I do reactions like this. And they go like, "Really?"
(From YouTube channels to major TV stations)
I see.
(An unlicensed self-made comedienne has become a rising variety star.)
This is Jang Mi Hee talking to her husband...
when he returns after staying out all night.
"Get out."
(Variety Show Fox Kim Ji Yu)
- "Get out right now." - That's it.
We have Jin Ho here today.
- They're the best. - And we have Ji Yu here.
(The two variety show siblings look quite alike.)
- She's here. - Hello.
Actually, today is quite meaningful because this is...
- Jin Ho's tenth appearance here. - Really?
(It's his 10th appearance!)
- Already? - Ji Yu's here for the first time.
(Ji Yu's first appearance on Running Man)
Right.
We've wanted to see you, Ji Yu.
- Right. - My mom and dad...
- told me this before. - You told them you'd be here?
No. They said they wanted to see me here.
(For a long time)
- I see. - They've always said that.
They said they wanted me to join Running Man.
And I'm finally here.
- I'm so happy. - There are many media outlets...
that have their own influence and charm these days,
(Each medium)
- but for parents, - That's right.
appearing on a major TV show is the best.
(Major TV stations are the best for parents.)
- It's the best. - This is SBS.
You should be on a TV show like this.
Of course.
Jin Ho, when you came here last time,
you had lost so much weight.
- Now you've gained the weight back. - You've filled out again.
(Plump)
- You were on Mounjaro back then. - Right. He was on Mounjaro.
(Just 6 months ago)
I lost weight using Mounjaro back then,
but the yo-yo effect hit me hard.
So I started getting it again last week.
(The yo-yo effect hit Moun Jin Ho hard.)
- I see. - By the way,
- What happened to your eyes? - your eyes...
(By the way)
- Did the surgery settle in now? - I think it settled in.
(6 months ago, Jin Ho had another ptosis surgery.)
- It's still a little... - His eyes are still uneven.
(Still uneven)
I think it got a lot better,
(Working to depuff his eyes for six months)
- but it hasn't settled in yet. - You mean this eye?
These eyes...
look just like Shim Hyung Rae's back in the day.
(The best compliment for entertainer Jin Ho)
- His eyes were a little... - Shim Hyung Rae?
He does look like him.
Jin Ho's situation keeps changing so fast...
every few months.
Now my daughter is...
(Updating them on becoming a girl's daddy)
20 months old already.
(Hong Ji Ah, 20 months old, Jin Ho's daughter)
- I'm living a happy life. - Congratulations.
- You must be happy. - Congratulations.
And about Ji Yu...
Everyone might have different preferences,
but Ji Yu shows up on my algorithm all the time.
You enjoy watching her.
(Algorithm-dominating crazy star power)
- Really? - She's really talented.
Ji Yu has her own dance moves.
It's insane.
- When she spots a guy she likes. - Yes.
Ji Yu is the only one...
who has mastered everything from nightclub moves to club dance.
- I know everything. - That's right.
(Full of confidence)
- She's mastered everything. - Right.
First, let me show you...
how it goes when I'm out with my friends.
- Can you be my friends here? - Sure.
(Situation 1: At the club with her girlfriends)
- Her female friends. - My friends.
- You should be her friends. - Wait.
She used to go to Don't Tell Mama. Are you sure it's okay?
(Club)
(The oldest is wearing a masquerade outfit.)
- Hey. - She went to Don't Tell Mama a lot.
Ji Hyo really looks like someone who actually came to a club.
Ji Yu, what are you doing with your shoulders?
- When you're at a club, - Because you're at a club?
- you should reveal your shoulders. - This is what you do at a club.
I'm seeing too many bare shoulders today.
(Shutting his eyes tight)
- You have to expose something. - Show some skin.
- You have to expose something. - Uncover your shoulders.
(Ye Eun joins in on the bare-shoulder look too.)
Show some skin.
- These three? - Now...
(Embarrassed)
It looks like...
you came to a club with your family on a national holiday.
- Ye Eun. - With the aunts.
(Aunt, Aunt, Eldest niece)
- All right. - We're friends.
This is when girls are hanging out at a club.
(Immersed)
Without any men.
- Is the music playing? - This is fun.
There you go.
There's no man.
(Cheering)
(Letting out a roar)
There's no men.
- Okay. - You're the best.
(Dancing)
There's no man!
(Shouting)
When there's no man.
Let's dance!
(Frightened)
(Even her friends turn their heads away from her moves.)
They're sick of it.
(Shocked and horrified)
(A stage fighter full of spirit)
All right.
- Now... - This is it.
(Stopped)
- So, this is... - Yes.
(Just now was her hanging out with her girlfriends)
- when you hang out with friends. - Exactly.
I'll show you how it goes when there's a man I'm attracted to.
(Situation 2: With a guy she's into)
- There's someone. - There's a man you like.
Music, please.
(Dongducheon Monkfish enters the club.)
(Winking)
(Oozing her pheromones)
(Looking away immediately)
How old are you?
Wait. By the way...
Your face looks completely sour. Look, Se Chan.
- It is sour! - But...
(What is?)
- Your moves are rotten. - Relax your face a bit.
You should play along.
(The girlfriends take Ji Yu's side.)
Wipe that look off your face.
- But you two just met. - Who would do that?
- When you just met him... - She was like this.
(Who shakes their shoulders at the first encounter?)
This is just too much.
Is this what young people do these days?
(The senior is curious.)
- Like this? - When I like someone,
- I make a bold move. - You make a bold move.
I approach him with a smile and do this.
(Nice!)
- I go like this. - Why is your mouth open so wide?
It's quite dusty there.
I saw way too much of her molars.
I thought you were a dentist.
I almost treated her teeth.
- It's quite dark in there. - I see.
And my mouth is my best feature, so...
If you open your mouth like that,
all your teeth will look they're glowing in the dark.
That's right. They're glowing.
(Flirting with glow-in-the-dark veneers)
That's what I intended.
(Ji Yu's endless charm will continue in just a moment.)
- I'll tell you about today's race. - Okay.
Today's race is called...
Let's All Take a Tour Around Jongno.
- A tour around Jongno. - Really?
- Around Jongno. - Jongno.
(Ready to go around)
- It's Jongno. - I love Jongno.
I love Gwanghwamun, Jongno, and Myeongdong.
There are so many good restaurants.
We will have a tour around Jongno,
(Jongno, packed with historic sites and delicious food)
the perfect travel spot...
with everything from historic sites to diverse food.
Okay.
We will be playing Jongno Marble,
featuring various iconic spots across Jongno.
- Jongno Marble! - Yes!
The 1st of the 2 teams to complete a full lap wins.
- I see. - Okay.
So this is like the board game Blue Marble.
There are penalties?
There are prize spaces and penalty spaces.
Teams landing on each space...
will earn either a prize or a penalty.
The winning team gets to keep their prizes,
(Prize)
while the losing team has to get their penalties.
(Penalty)
- Penalties? - Okay. It's simple.
Look at the prize.
- Tablet PC. - Tablet PC.
(Tablet PC)
- Tablet PC! - Yes!
- Are you giving it for real? - Yes.
(Tablet PC is one of the amazing prizes!)
If you land on the tablet PC space, which you love,
you'll get it as a prize.
They've never given us anything this good before.
Hang on.
Why is Ewha Girls' High School a penalty?
As you see, there are prize spaces and penalty spaces.
(The prize and penalty spaces have been randomly placed.)
They were just placed at random.
- I see. - Okay.
And the specific prize or penalty for each space...
will be revealed after the race.
Also, there are food spaces and cafe spaces.
(Food: Chinese cuisine or Naengmyeon, Cafe)
Only the team that lands on them...
gets to enjoy the meal or coffee.
If you don't land on them, you don't get to eat?
Seriously?
(Moun Jin Ho is shocked.)
While one team is having their meal,
the other team will be waiting on the bus.
- Oh, no. - My goodness.
- That's too harsh. - This is really cruel.
There will be two teams.
(Announcing the teams)
The first team is Yu Jae Seok, Yang Se Chan,
Ji Ye Eun, and Hong Jin Ho.
Kim Jong Kook, Kee Seok Jin, Haha,
Song Ji Hyo, and Kim Ki Yu are on the same team.
- Okay. - Good.
Now, change your outfits,
(Team Jae Seok, Team Jong Kook)
- and we will roll the first die. - Okay.
- Okay. - All right.
Okay.
(Which team will complete a full lap first?)
Yes!
Let's do this. Who will roll the die?
(The first die roll)
We will have our guest do it.
- Ji Yu. - Ji Yu should do it.
So we should make it back to the starting point, right?
Yes. It's over once you complete a full lap.
(Make it all the way around to complete the course)
Which number is good? Wait.
(They must avoid 4 or 6, the penalty spaces!)
Five is good.
Hey, it's okay.
- All right. - There you go.
- Five is good. - Okay!
- Okay! - Good. Five.
- What was that? - It's not acceptable.
- Why did you do that? - You can't do that.
- So it won't go over there. - Don't do that.
(Feeling awkward)
(The die rolled off Jae Seok's hand.)
Is this okay?
(What is the result?)
- Five? - Four!
It's three.
- Seoul Museum of History. - It's okay.
(Seoul Museum of History)
- It's three. - Seoul Museum of History.
It's not bad.
It's good, right? You got three because I touched the die.
(Avoided the penalty and arrived at the Museum of History)
It's the Seoul Museum of History. That's nice.
Let's make it quick.
(Jin Ho will roll the die for Team Jae Seok.)
- We will touch it for you. - You will get four.
- Touch it if it goes out. - Four.
- Five. - Six.
(He misses it.)
You missed it.
- Five. - Five.
Five!
- What is five? - Golden Key!
(Golden Key)
- Golden Key! - Golden Key!
- Nice. - Golden Key.
- Okay! - You did a great job.
We're off to a good start.
(Team Jae Seok secured a Golden Key.)
Sometimes Golden Key can be bad.
(Spoiling the mood)
- Ye Eun. - Ye Eun, you do it.
- But I'm Unlucky Hand. - You go.
(Golden Key is a random mix of good perks and penalties.)
There could be a penalty.
- Just pick one. - Go.
- Pick a penalty. - Just go with it.
- Something good. - Please.
It's something bad. Look at her face.
- "Move one space backward." - Move back?
(Move: Move 1 space backward.)
- It's a penalty! - Penalty!
(Penalty: Ewha Girls' High School)
(They moved backward right into a penalty.)
- What? - Penalty!
- Yes! It's a penalty! - What happens now?
- After landing on Golden Key. - Oh, no.
(The meaning behind the penalty space will be revealed later.)
- Okay. - Okay.
Between the spaces both teams landed on,
we'll head to the pre-approved spot...
- and carry out the mission there. - Okay. Let's go.
- Go to Ewha Girls' High School. - Ewha Girls' High School.
(Walking to Ewha Girls' High School)
Ewha Girls' High School is right here.
It's a three-minute walk.
All right. Let's go.
This is nice.
I absolutely love Jeongdong-gil here.
It's so lush and green. It's beautiful.
(The tranquil streets of Jeongdong-gil,)
This is nice.
(lined with lush ginkgo trees)
If you come here in the fall...
and listen to Lee Moon Sae's songs, it's just amazing.
- It's really nice. - I love Moon Sae's songs.
- Moon Sae! - On Jeongdong-gil down the hill
("Gwanghawmun Love Song")
- It's still remaining - This is the place.
This is incredible.
(The background to "Gwanghawmun Love Song" by Lee Moon Sae)
- This is... - I love...
how the old-school vibe is still alive here.
- This is the historic old downtown. - It's nice in all four seasons.
(The older ones are lost in the retro mood.)
It's beautiful.
I love the sound of the cicadas.
This is really nice.
Ji Yu, how does it feel walking like this on Running Man?
It's a dream come true.
- Ji Yu. - Yes?
- Don't stay over here. - Okay.
Stick right next to Jae Seok.
That way, you get the most screen time.
(Sharing pro tips)
- I see. - Go.
What is it, Jae Seok? Did you call me?
(Suddenly)
What? When did I call you?
(Flustered)
- Yes? - When?
(Securing airtime right away)
You called me.
- I didn't. - Yes, you called me.
- I didn't. - You did.
- There she goes. - I...
Ji Yu, I didn't call you.
(Closing off)
- I didn't. - No, you can talk to me.
- He says he didn't call her. - It's funny.
He says no.
Thank you so much for all your kind words.
- I did? - Seriously.
(It's new to me.)
I didn't say any kind words.
- Good, Ji Yu. - I feel like crying.
- Ji Yu. - You said so many nice things.
(Forcing a heartwarming story to secure airtime)
I didn't say anything nice.
She's so funny.
That's right. Hello!
Have a nice day.
(Superstar Jee's world-class act strikes again.)
Hi! Where are you from?
I'm from Canada!
(Citizen)
- Yes! - Canada!
You lived in Canada, right?
- Yes! - Who?
- What did he say? - No, you didn't.
- What did he say? - He asked if you lived in Canada.
- He asked if I lived in Canada? - Yes.
No!
(Urgently)
I live here!
Bye!
(Unable to tell who he mistook Seok Jin for)
Have a good day!
Seok Jin.
Why did you say yes when you didn't even understand it?
I didn't get it.
- When you didn't get it... - I thought he said,
"Are you Running Man?"
He didn't say anything about Running Man.
(While English-deaf Seok Jin almost became Canadian)
I see. I didn't know that.
- Why did you say that? - This is Ewha Girls' High School.
- Ewha Girls' High School. - Is this it?
(They have arrived at the destination.)
- Look at the buildings. - It's so close.
- Look at the buildings. - It's so pretty.
They are beautiful.
- The buildings look great. - Yes.
(This gorgeous building with red bricks is...)
Our first destination is...
the Simpson Memorial Hall of Ewha Girls' High School.
(First stop of Jongno Marble)
(Ewha Girls' High School Simpson Memorial Hall )
Founded in 1886,
this landmark has pioneered Korean women's education...
after receiving the name Ewha Haktang...
as Korea's first educational institution for women.
(Where the history of women's education in Korea...)
(has been preserved)
This is really cool.
This is the Ewha Museum.
This is really nice.
- Ewha Haktang. - Yu Gwan Sun.
So, Martyr Yu Gwan Sun...
- went to this school? - Yes.
Back then,
she joined the March 1 Independence Movement at Ewha Haktang.
- That's right. - Martyr Yu Gwan Sun?
(The alma mater of independence activist Yu Gwan Sun)
- This is my first time here. - This is meaningful and nice.
I've never been here before.
(The well where Yu Gwan Sun actually did her laundry...)
- It's so meaningful and nice. - Ewah Haktang.
(while living in the dormitory.)
Back in the day, I mean.
- Ewha Museum. - This is so cool.
(The members drink in the traces...)
- Check this out. - These ancestors shaped history.
(left here and there.)
There was nothing around here.
- You're right. - Only fields.
Turns out she was an elite.
(The Ewha Hakdang students actively fought for independence.)
- That was rare back then. - Tell me about it.
- You're right. - It was back in the 1910s.
- Over here. - What is this place?
(Inside the museum)
- No way. - I can't believe it.
- Historically speaking... - My gosh.
(A collection of works by Ewha Girls' High School graduate artists)
- This is so cool. - Tell me about it.
- Check out the art pieces. - This place is amazing.
- This place is beautiful. - Check out the ceiling.
- This one's pretty. - I'm loving the artwork.
That's so cool.
(An elegant wooden ceiling...)
- What is this? - This is really cool.
(and captivating works of art)
- It looks like yutnori. - No way.
- Are you kidding me? - That's eye-catching.
Right. Over here, guys.
- Jin Ho. - They look like they're falling.
- Ji Yu... - Yes?
She keeps coming to us when she's not on our team.
Ji Yu, get over here.
- Instinctively... - Did someone call me?
(Sticking close)
- I don't like this. - Did you call me?
(Securing airtime by sticking close to Jae Seok)
- Instinctively, she... - That's not it.
- Get over here. - I keep hearing Jae Seok's voice.
(Hearing things)
- What? - "Ji Yu." Like this?
(Smiling bitterly)
- What? - That's understandable.
I never said anything sweet to her, but she keeps thanking me.
- Stop forcing it. - She showed tears too.
- Why would you show tears? - Seriously. Thank you.
- I haven't been sweet to her. - It's okay.
- Right. - It's all good.
We'll now begin the next game.
Team Jae Seok landed a penalty.
- That's right. - Of course.
Each of them gets a penalty ball.
As they should.
Write their names on them.
- Nice. - Congratulations.
(Acting cheeky)
- Nice! - Do we write down...
- each of our names? - No.
No, please write down anyone you'd like.
(Write down the name of the member you want on the penalty ball.)
Jae Seok, we can write down whoever we want.
- I see. - Anyone on the team? I see.
(An ally who turned out to be an enemy)
It's every man for himself.
Really?
They can't put our names down.
(Glancing)
- They can't put our names down. - Let's keep each other safe.
- I promise. - Really?
(Kong Jin Ho teams up with Ddochi.)
Jae Seok, they made a pact.
- What? Hold on. - They formed an alliance.
That's not it. I just asked her a question.
- Each other, right? - I'll write down my name.
- I'll write my name down too. - You're lying.
- Let's write down our names. - Should we all...
write down our names?
Me too.
(Keeping a distance)
Write down Jae Seok's name.
(Ventriloquism)
(Ssaebssaeb betrays right away.)
Are we writing someone else's name?
No, just someone on our team.
- I see. - Can you stand over there?
But why... Come on!
Let's write down our names.
(Jae Seok)
(Ye Eun and Jin Ho wrote Jae Seok.)
- They're ganging up on Jae Seok. - Okay, fine!
- I see what you're doing. - Jae Seok, you can only choose one.
Even if you know, there's nothing you can do about it.
- Exactly. It's 3 to 1. - Got it.
- Let's do this. - Let's carry on.
(Hong Jin Ho)
(Jae Seok added a penalty ball for Jin Ho.)
- I wrote my own name. - There.
(Yu Jae Seok, Jae Seok, Yu Jae Seok, Hong Jin Ho)
- I wrote my own name too. - Me too.
- Jae Seok's on his own. - It's over for him.
(Team Jae Seok's Penalty Box)
- I'm declaring war now. - Okay.
(3 Yu Jae Seok, 1 Hong Jin Ho)
- Seriously. I'm declaring war. - Come on.
(Team Jae Seok's penalty balls have been added.)
The game you'll play here...
is Swinging in the Dark!
(Mission 1 of Let's All Take a Tour Around Jongno)
- What's that? - In the dark?
One from each team will compete.
While blindfolded,
they'll grab the table with one hand...
and grab a pillow in the other.
- I see. - Blindfolded?
Each player gets two chances to attack.
They can swing whenever they want,
and a successful hit earns a point.
What if we throw it?
The team with the higher overall score wins.
- We get to swing once. - Back and forth, right?
I have a feeling Se Chan will be good at this.
- Didn't I hit you once? - Yes.
(Looking forward to Running Man's 2nd strongest)
- Se Chan also... - I think you'll be good.
- Round 1. - How about Ye Eun for Round 1?
(Filmed safely with the cooperation and supervision of museum staff.)
How about Ji Yu and Ye Eun...
(First)
- face off? - Who's older?
- Sounds good. - Ji Yu, of course.
- She's older. - Is Ye Eun older?
- Hey! - What?
- What? - Hey?
(4 years older)
Isn't Ye Eun older?
Right, you're younger.
(Embarrassed)
Make his gums collapse.
(Mumbling)
Who's playing in Round One?
We'll start with Ye Eun.
(Team Jae Seok: Ye Eun versus Team Jong Kook: Ji Yu)
- Sounds good. Ji Yu, then. - Ji Yu.
- Come on out. - Sure.
Go, Ji Yu.
- I'm scared of her. - I feel bad about hitting her.
She does look like she'll hit hard.
I bet she's no joke.
(Cracking)
The smaller, the feistier.
- I mean... - That's true.
I'm not kidding...
when I say she looks an awful lot like someone I know.
Really? A guy or a girl?
- A guy or a girl? - A guy.
- A guy? - A guy?
Im Woo Il.
(Correct!)
- Im Woo Il? - Nice!
- Nice. - Hey, nice.
She looks an awful lot like someone I know.
Ji Yu, you look so stable.
(His appearance sends expectations through the roof.)
I don't think she can knock you down.
Ji Yu is so...
- Should the table stay there? - Ye Eun.
Where can we run if the table's there?
- Is it there for us to grab? - We're supposed to grab it.
(Seok Jin didn't listen to the rules again.)
I don't think it should be there.
The table has to be there for us to safely run around.
(Kind)
Would you like to go first?
- No, you go first. - Okay, I'll go first.
- Get ready. - I'm scared.
(Kim Ji Yu is on offense first.)
- Ye Eun, play defense. - Duck.
(Ddochi is on defense.)
(Only 1 swing per attack is allowed.)
Set...
Keep going. Faster.
(Ye Eun crawls out of range.)
- Faster. - It's getting scary.
- That was scary. - Wait, I heard something.
Wait, I heard something.
(Rustling)
(Her nylon pants give away her location.)
What?
(Aiming at nothing)
(No, not there.)
Swing. Now's the time!
Swing.
(No, it's not there.)
(Changing her aim)
Swing. Now's the time!
(Thud!)
(A direct hit to the back of the head)
Right in the back of her head!
- No way. - Hold on a second.
- Seriously. - Come on.
- Don't tip her off. - What did I do?
(Immediately calling out Seok Jin's sneaky move)
- Seriously. - All I did was this.
- You tipped her off. - How did I tip her off?
- I was going to say something. - I didn't hear him.
- Seriously. - Hold on.
(What I did)
- That? - That sound he made.
- Go again. - Did I tip her off?
(Seok Sam owns up to it.)
Seok Jin, I heard you!
- Just hit him already. - Did you hear me?
(Jae Seok wants to discipline him with a spank.)
- Not at all. - Hit him.
- Ji Yu, be honest with me. - You heard him, didn't you?
- Ji Yu. - Hold on.
- Guys, I'll speak up. - Sure. Go ahead.
I heard him.
Whose side are you on?
- I'm just being honest. - Pick the right side, will you?
(Betrayed by the trusted Ji Yu)
- I was only trying to help. - Nice!
(Jee Seok Jin is to be punished.)
- It's my side you should take. - That's not it.
(Ji Yu takes this chance to gain brownie points.)
- I'm just being honest. - Seok Jin, get down here.
- I can't help what I heard. - Lie down on your stomach.
Age doesn't even matter here, okay?
- Age isn't a factor. - Being wrong deserves a beating.
- That's right. - Exactly.
- Seok Jin. - I get it, okay?
(Disciplining Seok Jin in hopes of breaking his bad habit)
That's true.
- Cheating is wrong. - Right.
I won't offend him in any way,
(Gripping the pillow hard)
- and just lightly tap his face. - Sounds good.
- Sure. - That doesn't even look dangerous.
- Just one simple tap. - Put your hands in your pockets.
- I'll keep them here. - You'll look less pathetic.
(Hand on the waist)
Seok Jin, put them in your pockets.
(Sliding in)
- What about his glasses? - You should take them off.
That could be dangerous.
All right. It'll be one simple tap.
(Troublemaker Seok is obedient.)
- Sure. - It won't hurt.
I doubt this will hurt.
(Thud!)
(A sneaky hit that leaves you feeling salty)
That wasn't the best feeling.
- That upset him. - That was better.
- All right. - Let's continue.
(Resuming the game after disciplining Seok Sam)
- You can't tip them off. - Let's do this.
- Don't tip each other off. - That wasn't a nice feeling.
(Sneaky moves are prohibited from now on.)
Don't tip each other off.
That didn't count, right?
- That didn't count. - Hit reset.
(The earlier round doesn't count.)
- That didn't count. - Unbelievable.
Check left or right before starting.
(Ji Yu's on the offense again.)
Run!
(Screaming)
- I'm scared. - What the...
Don't make a sound!
- Why are you talking? - Why make a sound?
(Ddochi literally told her location.)
Why did you suddenly speak?
- That's not it. - Why would you make a sound?
- Hold on. - Why would you make a sound?
You can hear her breathing heavily.
She was like this.
(Breathing heavily)
Unbelievable.
I'm scared.
What was that?
I thought there was a beast in here.
(Terrified)
(Team Jae Seok: 0, Team Jong Kook: 1)
- You could've ducked. - Cover your ears, then.
- Ye Eun, do better. - Okay.
(Ye Eun is on offense this time.)
Grab the table.
- Good. - Ready, set...
- Take that. - Don't make a sound.
(Swinging)
Ye Eun, your attack failed.
- What? - Was that it?
You can't swing like that, Ye Eun.
(Ye Eun blew her chance to attack!)
- She already blew her chance. - Who attacked?
- Don't swing like that! Come on! - What on earth?
(Ji Ddochi annoys everyone.)
- Did I do something wrong? - Ye Eun... Time out.
- Didn't you understand the rules? - You only get to swing once.
- You lose your chance to attack. - Don't swing aimlessly like that.
(An airhead to the point that the game can't resume)
- I see. - Why were you swinging earlier?
- She's impossible, isn't she? - It's all right.
- Swing after you locate her. - Come on.
(Swing after you find her!)
- Sorry about that. - Get a grip on yourself.
- You only get to swing once. - Ye Eun, get a grip on yourself.
(The guys hold back and cheer her up with nice words.)
- You can do it. - Stay calm and don't be scared.
She doesn't hit that hard.
(Team Jae Seok: 0, Team Jong Kook: 1)
- I didn't know. - You've got to be kidding me.
(Ji Yu is on offense again.)
- Okay, let's go. - Don't be scared of her.
(Panting)
My gosh.
- Seriously? - Stop making those sounds!
(A hit to the head)
- Why would you do that? - Don't make any sounds.
Why is she making those sounds?
Why would you make sounds like that?
(Ddochi scored an own point twice.)
What's wrong with you?
(Team Jae Seok: 0, Team Jong Kook: 2)
(The score gap widened because of her.)
- You shouldn't be making sounds. - But...
I don't want to make those sounds,
but what can I do when it can't be stopped?
I'll pluck your teeth out!
Do you want your gums to collapse?
Okay, let's do it again.
(No complaining)
Think before you swing, okay?
(Ye Eun's last chance to attack)
- Unbelievable. - Swing...
- after you locate her. - You only have one chance.
Ye Eun, step up.
(Blow up this chance as well, and the guys will get furious.)
- Just get in there. - Find her first.
Ye Eun, step up.
Ye Eun, you need to hit her this time.
(Carefully)
Swing across the table.
(Close to making contact)
Okay!
(Thud!)
(Ye Eun finally lands an attack.)
Does that bring the score to 2 to 1?
- Yes! Did I win? - The scores will be added.
(Team Jae Seok: 1, Team Jong Kook: 2)
- I can't do this again. - Nice.
- You should take Jong Kook on. - Ye Eun...
- Me? - It'd be funnier that way.
(Flustered)
- Me? - Yes, go ahead.
Jong Kook, what do you say?
(Down by 1 point, sending in the game-changer Kong)
Why don't you go against Jin Ho?
Jin Ho, go ahead.
I'm fine taking on just anyone.
(Great Physique Gym Jong Kook versus Mr. Intelligent Hong Jin Ho)
Okay. Getting hit with a pillow won't hurt much anyway.
(Relaxed)
You'll think differently once you get hit by it.
Who attacks first?
- Rock-paper-scissors? - Sure.
- Rock-paper... - Ready or not, rock...
- Rock... - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Jin Ho has won.)
What on earth was he saying?
- Jong Kook. - Jong Kook, look.
Rock-paper-scissors!
(Upset)
(His pronunciation gets worse when he's excited.)
Jong Kook, it was "ready or not."
(Translator)
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Ready or not,
- rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
"Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors."
Ready or not? I see.
(He understood.)
- Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors. - Got it.
Now I'm offended.
He just said he was offended.
"Now I'm offended."
Rock-paper-scissors.
Okay, got it.
(Either way, Jin Ho is on offense first.)
Jin Ho's on the offense. Ready...
Wait. Okay, got it.
(Round 2 begins.)
He talks a lot like Hyung Rae too.
(Circling in the same direction)
- I mean, this is... - Who's on the offense?
(Suddenly)
Jin Ho?
(Jin Ho slides right under the table.)
Under the table?
Is it Jin Ho?
- No way. - Under the table?
(Jong Kook steps aside as soon as they make contact.)
Jin Ho hit him.
(He follows Jong Kook and lands his attack!)
What was that?
Nice.
(Jin Ho scores 1 point.)
- What was that? - Okay!
(Scored a point by using the table)
- Should the table stay there? - Ye Eun.
Where can we run if the table's there?
(The table in the middle seemed random.)
I don't think it should be there.
The table has to be there for us to safely run around.
Ye Eun, step up.
(During Round 1)
Ye Eun, wouldn't it be faster to grab the table?
(As Ji Yu and Ye Eun play without a strategy,)
That's why they put the table there.
(the former pro gamer observes closely.)
- That was clever. - How bold was that?
(Used a strategy to cover up his yo-yo-stricken body)
- Seriously. - That was...
- a clever play from Jin Ho. - He was a pro gamer.
That was scary smart.
(Team Jae Seok: 2, Team Jong Kook: 2)
- Nice. - The genius gamer.
- The StarCraft player. - That was great.
Go, Zerg Master.
(Jong Kook on offense)
He thinks differently, doesn't he?
That was fast, and you couldn't hear him at all.
(Jin Ho's strategy is to hide.)
- That strategy. - He's different.
There's a time limit.
(Hiding in a corner far away from the previous attack)
(Will Jong Kook notice it?)
That's it.
Jong Kook...
(Testing with his foot)
He's different.
- There's a time limit. - That's it.
(Jong Kook checks where the previous attack was from.)
Jong Kook...
(Reaching out)
Jong Kook is confused now.
(It seems his strategy is working again!)
That hurts.
Gosh. Right in the corner...
- What the... - Come on.
(Seok Sam ruins it again.)
He deserves a slap.
A punch.
Gosh. Right in the corner...
What the...
(The corner?)
Come on.
(Wincing)
(Jong Kook passes by.)
Watch the time.
No.
(Look at him!)
Two slaps. That's the second one.
(He's going to take 2 hits.)
I'll count down now. Five,
(5-second countdown)
- You're staying on one side. - four,
- Where... - three, two,
- To your right. - one.
(Telling him again)
- Jong Kook failed. - What?
(Despite Seok Sam's fouls, the attack was a failure.)
What?
- What a strategy. - Good job.
(He defended with ease.)
That was a really good idea.
That was incredible.
- Someone needs a beating. - Seriously.
- A punishment. - He must pay.
- Seok Jin deserves two hits. - Two hits.
- He interfered? - The two of them...
- He made noises. - You won anyway.
(Let it slide.)
- Still. - You messed up.
- You must pay. - You won anyway.
- You deserve it. - It can't be helped.
We said this would happen.
(Come here.)
You won anyway.
(He's getting ready while complaining.)
- Two hits. - Yes, two.
- Why am I being punished? - This is...
(Complaining)
- Why? - For making noises.
(Team Jae Seok)
- You said too many things. - You won in the end.
Tap him on the nose with a slight nudge.
(Nudge)
(Punishing the senior is complete.)
That's it.
(Crooked)
- That was really annoying. - Seok Jin's pouting.
(Team Jae Seok: 2, Team Jong Kook: 2)
(1 point, 0 points)
The score is 1 to 0.
Jin Ho will attack first. Are you ready?
(Jin Ho's final attack)
(Jong Kook must evade.)
Go.
(Standing still)
What's going on?
(Why is he doing that?)
(Jong Kook stands still instead of running away.)
What the... No!
(Kook pushes Jin Ho backward.)
What was that?
(Jin Ho's attack failed.)
- Hang on. - Why?
He pushed me.
He got pushed!
(Panting in anger)
That's one option.
(Kim Muscles has decided to just use his strength.)
- What was that? - Hey.
- What was that? - That was my strategy!
I ran away.
Who says you can't push your opponent?
(His strategy is to use his physicality to win.)
I'm glad he's on my team.
It felt like being pushed by a huge slab of concrete.
(It felt like being pushed by a huge slab of concrete.)
Jin Ho acts like Shim Hyung Rae too.
- My plan was to... - "No!"
(The return of village idiot Yeong Goo)
- You were like... - I mean...
(Every time he comes, he creates a new character.)
He pushed me.
The time limit...
Okay. I got it.
(The 2nd round ended with Jong Kook's loss.)
- Jin Ho's... - This is really...
- Okay... - Get the win.
(Team Jae Seok: 2, Team Jong Kook: 2)
- It's two all right now. - Ssaebssaeb, you...
- That was fun. - You need to score.
It's really scary.
(Round 3, Se Chan versus Haha)
- You did well. - Rock-paper-scissors.
- I'll attack first. - Okay.
(Se Chan attacks first.)
You did well.
If you're going to hit me, use the pillow.
(Whispering)
What...
(Scared)
Don't use your hands, okay?
Don't worry.
- What is it? - What's going on?
(A fierce showdown is expected.)
I'm scared to go against you.
- I'm ready. - Hang on.
(Who will become the winner today?)
This is really scary.
This round...
Set...
(Round 3 begins.)
(Staying in the corner like Jin Ho)
(Will Se Chan notice?)
(He's getting closer!)
(Hold your breath!)
(Get him!)
(Quick turn!)
(He passes by?)
(Nudge)
(Got you)
We don't know yet.
Hang on. I'm not sure yet.
(The piranha successfully hooked a human.)
I'm not sure yet.
(Trembling)
Wait. I don't know where he is. Where are you? Hang on.
(Nasty)
Let me see.
(A full swing)
(He gains a point with a feel-good whack!)
Seriously?
- It's over. - Well done.
(Team Jae Seok: 3, Team Jong Kook: 2)
Nice one.
(Haha was crushed.)
- Please... - It was close.
(Coughing)
Get revenge! Haha!
(Shouting)
- You can do it! - Hang on.
(It's Haha's turn to attack.)
- Haha! - Go for it, Haha!
- Ready, go. - Go for it!
- That's it. Go with speed. - Okay!
(He's in the corner.)
- Okay! - Speed is good!
- That's it. Go with speed. - Okay!
(He's searching for him while shaking.)
- Speed is good! - Okay.
Speed is good, but...
- Okay. - Okay!
That's it! Right there!
(Swinging)
Darn you!
(His attack failed.)
- Hey! - Are you that stupid?
Good job, Se Chan!
- Nice one. - Well done.
(He made a big fuss, only to fail.)
Hey! If you don't feel any legs...
You should've checked the corners. You saw what happened to me.
(Frustrated)
(Se Chan attacks again.)
- You need to move fast. - Ready, set...
(Rustling)
The noise...
(What's that noise?)
(He made contact?)
(I got you again.)
I didn't hit him yet.
(Excited)
(Haha got fooled again.)
Hold on. I'm not yet sure where he is.
(He finds the perfect angle.)
(Another full swing)
Was that a hit? I hit him.
(Team Jae Seok: 4, Team Jong Kook: 2)
- You're good at this. - Nicely done.
Well done!
(Haha allowed Team Jae Seok to take the lead.)
- Nice one. - You're the ace.
- Nicely done. - Nice one!
- Well done. - Nice.
- Haha, go for it. - One more time.
(Haha's last chance to attack)
- Okay. - Nice one.
- Win for us once. - We need this point.
Haha, let's win this one.
Haha. It's a team thing.
- That's enough, Haha. - We need a point.
- Nice one. - Let's go.
(Mr. Dirty Mustache needs to score.)
We need to win one, at least.
- He attacks. - No.
(The game resumes.)
- He attacks. - Haha attacks this time.
Oh, right.
(Ears perked)
(Going off-route)
What are you doing?
You're not hiding this time, Haha.
(Searching the wrong area)
You're the seeker.
Get a grip, Haha.
(Sighing)
(Showing off poorly)
(Just then)
(He's heading toward Se Chan?)
- I'm scared. - He's like a zombie.
(Immersed)
(Reaching out)
Oh, gosh.
(Laughing)
(That's the spot!)
(A sudden U-turn)
(Haha blew his chance to win.)
What an amazing...
Counting down from five,
(5-second countdown)
- Hurry up! - four,
- three, two, - Move to the side!
(Holding his breath)
- one. You failed. - Okay!
(Swinging)
(His attack failed.)
Okay!
- That was scary. - Nice one.
(Team Jae Seok: 4, Team Jong Kook: 2)
You did well. It's okay.
It's not easy at all.
It's Seok Sam and me this time.
(The last players, Jae Seok versus Seok Jin)
We must win this round.
(The team's fate is in the hands of these older brothers.)
- A tie is fine. - Seriously.
- I'll win. You think I can't? - Good luck!
- Good luck, Seok Jin! - I'll bring home the win.
- I will... - We must win this time.
(The gap is 2 points now.)
You can do it.
(Whether he's attacking or defending, if he fails just once,)
I'll bring home the win.
What do you want to do?
(Team Jae Seok wins and it's game over.)
- I'll go first. - Okay.
- I'm it? - Yes.
(Seok Jin attacks first.)
- You can do it. - Let's win!
(The winning team will be decided in the final round.)
Good luck!
Seok Jin attacks first. Are you ready?
Start.
(The game begins.)
(Jae Seok stands in a corner.)
(A nervous sigh)
No.
(Getting closer)
(A glancing touch)
(The random kicks made contact!)
(Taekwon Boy's fancy moves)
(He kicks in the wrong direction.)
- Oh, dear... - I felt something.
This is so scary!
- We're done for. - That kick must hurt.
(Quick judgment)
- Gosh. - He's so fast.
(Right then)
He's so fast.
Yes, nice.
(Moving fast toward Jae Seok!)
That's it.
(Presses hard)
(He swung!)
(A determined full swing! Will it land?)
(Falling)
- It was a hit. - It made contact.
- It counts. - That counts.
(Seok Sam's attack was successful!)
- He did it. - He scored.
- I hit him. - You got him!
(Young Sixty threw himself and won!)
You got hit in the calf.
That was a good hit. You got him good.
(Team Jae Seok: 4, Team Jong Kook: 3)
- That was really... - Jae Seok attacks now.
- Ready, set... - It's so tense.
(Jae Seok needs just 1 point to win.)
(Sitting at the same time)
(They hit it off when they shouldn't.)
No.
(Bump)
(We're done for!)
No.
He missed!
(What?)
It didn't touch.
(He got away!)
He missed!
- What happened? - Okay!
(Flustered)
He missed!
(Jee-rasoni got away.)
It didn't touch.
(Surprised)
- What happened? - He got away.
- What happened? - He missed!
(Jae Seok's attack failed.)
(Team Jae Seok: 4, Team Jong Kook: 3)
It was a miss.
(Team Jong Kook has a chance to even the score.)
- I really didn't get hit. - You didn't?
- What happens now? - It missed. Seok Jin attacks.
Ready.
(It's Jee-rasoni's last chance.)
Looking good. That's cool.
(If Seok Sam can't hit him, he'll lose.)
Okay.
- It doesn't help to make noise. - How is that...
(Kicking harder, thinking he's the main character)
(Too into his role)
Is he here?
(Blocking)
(Blocking Seok Sam with the table)
(Snorting laugh)
(But that gave away his location.)
(Breathing heavily)
Okay!
(Got you)
(Flapping and flailing)
(The grasshopper fights back.)
(He missed it!)
Where are you?
(Seok Sam is blocked by the table!)
Swing it now!
(Plop)
- The pillow... - It's right there!
(Panting)
(He missed both the grasshopper and the pillow.)
- It's there. - What the...
Your pillow!
He doesn't know where the pillow is.
- The pillow! - Where is the pillow?
(In a rush)
- The pillow! - Five, four,
(Last 5 seconds)
three, two,
- Just throw it! - one!
(Throwing)
You failed to attack.
(Seok Sam's attack failed.)
He lost his pillow.
How could you drop the pillow?
(That's ridiculous.)
It slipped out of my hand.
(Seok Sam couldn't become a hero.)
You should have held on tight.
I was trying to hit him properly.
(Team Jong Kook lost.)
We lost, right?
(Meanwhile, Grasshopper dodged his way to victory.)
(Cheering)
Team Jae Seok won.
(Team Jae Seok wins the mission.)
- Nice. - Well done.
- Gosh. - Nice.
Will more be added?
Why don't we write our own names?
- That's a good idea. - Okay.
- Our own names? - Very nice.
(Looking away)
Looks like a crew is starting to form there.
Someone's crew needs to form...
We're writing our own names. Okay.
(Despite what they say, they're looking away.)
Our own names. Good.
(I got it.)
Seok Sam, you should get some penalty.
(Having a bad feeling)
The members of Team Jae Seok that won...
will get two balls each.
The members of Team Jong Kook that lost...
- will get one ball each. - Okay.
- The penalty. - It's the prize ball, right?
The balls you earned through this mission...
can be used as a prize ball or a penalty ball.
You should definitely put it in the prize box.
- You should make it a prize ball. - A prize ball.
We don't need to...
- make it bad for others. - Of course.
I should put it in the prize box.
I'm going to put it in the prize box too.
(Jae Seok)
That's only natural.
(He wrote his name on both balls as he promised.)
I wrote my name. Look.
I also wrote my name.
(Ye Eun also writes her name.)
I should put it in the prize box.
(Glancing)
- That's a given. - I wrote my name.
Should I put them in the box?
Let's go for the prize.
(Is she writing Jin Ho instead of her name?)
Let's go.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Put them in, Ye Eun. - Seriously.
(She puts the Jin Ho ball in the penalty box.)
Look at that. We all have one for each.
- I'm just going to put them here. - Really?
Our team has no trust.
There's no trust.
(Jae Seok wrote his name on both balls.)
(Erasing)
- You're crossing it out? - Why are you crossing it out?
- You're crossing it out? - In here...
I'm going to...
put one ball for Ye Eun in this box.
- Because she did well? - She did well.
(Is he taking care of Ddochi because he's proud of her?)
- We won thanks to Ye Eun. - That's right.
That's true, isn't it?
- I'll admit that. - I'll give her that.
Yes. So I'll...
(He writes Ye Eun's name.)
put it here.
He put it in.
(Putting it in the penalty box)
It made a sound when it dropped.
- She did well. - Did you do the shell game?
(He scolds him with his sleight of hand.)
- It made that sound. - It was like the shell game.
- We should go with the prize. - Of course.
(The members of Team Jong Kook only have 1 name ball each.)
We should definitely put them in the prize box.
We should put them in the prize box.
We have no reason to put the balls in the penalty box.
- The penalty... - Reasonably speaking.
You're trying to mess with others if you put them in the penalty box.
Right. That's...
(Ji Yu chose Seok Jin.)
- Yes. - We should put it in the prize box.
We should put them in the prize box.
(She puts it in the penalty box.)
I'll do the reasonable thing.
- In the penalty box? - What?
I think you just put the ball in the penalty box.
(Pretending not to know)
Did I put it in the wrong box?
Why aren't you putting your balls in the box?
Why would we put the balls in the penalty box?
(Seok Sam wrote Ji Yu's name.)
You can see it.
Why are you putting it in the penalty box?
- What? - Sir.
(He even got caught while doing that.)
- I mean... - What did you do?
- Why are you announcing that? - Sir.
- Why are you announcing that? - Everyone can see you.
"Why are you announcing that?"
(They secretly gave each other a penalty ball.)
They all saw me write my name. Didn't you?
- I didn't. - The penalty box...
- I didn't write on it. - She also...
(Whose balls will end up in which box the most?)
put hers in the penalty box.
You'd be tired from using your energy.
Have a candy to wake yourselves up.
- A candy? - Really?
I really wanted to have a candy right now.
I guess it's the one that clears your nose.
It really wakes you up.
(A refreshing flavor that clears the nose)
- It's good. - It's crunchy.
The texture is amazing.
- It's... - It's got a menthol flavor.
I really like the menthol flavor.
(Food Fighter also likes it.)
- It clears your nose. - Right?
It's refreshing. It's perfect for a little refresh.
(They fight off the sluggish feeling.)
We're going to move to the next location.
(It's time to roll the dice again.)
One representative from each team will roll the die.
Okay! Let's go.
(Team Jae Seok is 1 space ahead.)
Let's go. Okay.
Our team's hero.
- Ye Eun should do it. - Ye Eun...
(Ye Eun from Team Jae Seok will go first.)
- should throw. - Yes, I'll throw.
- Nice. - I'm unlucky, though.
I'm unlucky.
(Worried)
We saw how you did earlier.
- Just avoid rolling a two. - Two and five.
(Penalty: Memorial Hall)
(They just have to avoid Penalty 2 and Deserted Island 5.)
The others are fine. Four.
- Where are you? - We're here.
Just don't roll a 2 and a 5.
(What number will the unlucky Ddochi roll?)
- Two. - Two!
Two!
- Two. - Come on.
- It's a four. - That was intentional.
- That was intentional! - No!
- It's a four! - Four.
(Heading to Ju Si Gyung Square after earning a prize)
- Today, I'm... - You're doing great today.
(There's a huge gap now.)
- I'm doing great today. - You're amazing.
- It's your day. - It really is.
What do we need to roll? Hold on.
(Team Jong Kook goes next.)
Fried rice is also nice.
Could you move aside?
(Hitting)
Why are you hitting me so hard?
- Seok Sam. - Seok Jin!
(The strong man can't control his strength.)
You hit me so hard.
We need to avoid rolling a 1 or a 3.
- We need to avoid 1 and 3. - We shouldn't get 1 or 3.
(Team Jong Kook's goal is to avoid penalties.)
- Let's roll a two. - Two.
Two.
(Penalty: Memorial Hall, Penalty: Ewha Girls' High School)
- Two! - Two is nice.
That was weak.
- It's weak! - One.
One!
(No 1s or 3s!)
- That was weak. - It's not a one.
- It's weak. - One.
- One. - One!
- A penalty. - It's a penalty.
(They land on a penalty space.)
- It's Ewha Girls' High School. - For this...
- They get penalty balls. - They get penalty balls.
(Everyone on Team Jong Kook gets 1 penalty ball.)
- They should put one ball in there. - They should put one there.
- They should put one there. - So...
(Feeling anxious)
(The dice rolls with mixed results ends.)
- It's okay. - This is so nice.
I'll put mine in the prize box.
(Team Jae Seok is 4 spaces ahead.)
We should really put them in the prize box.
I'm going to put them in the prize box.
Let's go.
(They're going to Ju Si Gyung Square.)
This is like paradise.
(Showing off his throat)
Sit here, Ji Yu.
- Sit here, Ji Yu. - What?
(He singles out one spot and recommends it.)
- Sit here. - Okay.
That's Seok Jin's place, though.
You can sit there.
- Seok Jin never gives up this seat. - You know me.
(Seok Sam's permanent spot by the window)
I like leaning to the right.
Why? Why is this your seat?
Tell us. Tell us here.
(Despite countless challenges, he's never given up his spot.)
(It's Seok Sam's favorite spot.)
Keep playing dumb until the very end.
Then the audio director...
(Seok Sam's spot is under threat.)
Ji Yu.
- Tell him you get carsick. - Okay.
(Got it)
- You get carsick in other seats. - Okay.
I should take a picture of Seok Jin's expression from here.
It's hot.
(Seok Sam, the target, appears.)
It's so humid today.
- It's hot. - You're having fun.
(She starts acting, and he starts filming.)
It's so hot.
- Okay! - Nice.
- My head. - This is a good spot.
(Acting her heart out)
(Se Chan's camera)
It's a very...
- My head... - Ji Yu.
(Perplexed)
It's a good spot.
Did you watch Running Man a lot?
(You know that's my seat, right?)
- No. I'm getting carsick... - Carsick?
(He gets anxious after his seat gets stolen.)
- She's getting carsick. - Well...
Running Man...
- It's okay. Feel comfortable. - Take a nap.
(She's going all out pretending to be carsick.)
- I... - Are you all right?
- Press on her hand. - Hold on.
- This... - This is Seok Jin's seat.
(He gets kicked to the other seat.)
- You can sit there. - Jae Seok can go to the back.
- Okay. - Right here.
(Laughing)
Should I sit here?
Ji Yu, that's...
You're having a hard time, aren't you?
(She's even mindful of her hands while acting.)
- She's carsick. - I mean...
- Ji Yu. - When you get carsick,
(Helping)
you should sit at the end.
- Right. Lean on that. - You should look out the window.
(Helping)
- It's okay. - You should look out the window.
I'm a bit surprised, but it's okay.
You'll feel better if you stretch your leg...
- to this side. - Really?
- That's right. - Not like that. Stretch them here.
(Haha is going all out and having fun.)
- No. This way. - This way?
- That's right. - Okay.
- So this... - You look comfortable now.
I'll stop now.
- Well done. - I might get criticized.
(She stops him after getting her share of screen time.)
- You should make it clear. - Well done.
- I might get criticized. - You should be clear.
- I'm scared. - Well...
Things Haha tells you to do...
always have risks. You should know that.
It's funny,
- but you get criticized. - That's right.
(People tend to have mixed reactions to his jokes.)
- So, Ji Yu, you should... - People either love it or hate it.
- You'll have to deal with that. - The things he thinks are funny...
are pretty polarizing. So...
Don't be afraid of getting criticized.
You'll get criticized anyway.
- Modokkodong. - Either way.
- Modokkodong? - Modokkodong.
- Modokkodong. - Modokkodong.
- Where's Hong Jin Ho? - Modokkodong.
- I understand how you feel. - Jin Ho...
- You understand me, right? - "I understand."
(Only Jin Ho understands perfectly.)
- "Even if it's not funny." - "Even if it's not funny."
"I understand what you said."
It's embarrassing.
Jin Ho...
Jin Ho is really...
He's what you'd call a "chameleon" in the old days.
- A chameleon. - Every time he comes here,
(Chameleon with different charms)
- he's a different person. - That's true.
- He's a chameleon. - Today...
He's been winking all day today,
(Is that a compliment?)
- and it's so charming. - Seriously.
He came back after gaining some weight.
(Is that a compliment?)
His eyes look like Shim Hyung Rae's.
(The chubby cameleon's wink is addictive.)
I'll come back next time after losing some weight.
- You look good right now. - That's right. You look great.
Right.
That's right. You look good.
- Ji Yu. - Yes?
What's your nickname?
I have a few.
There's Im Woo Il...
(Ji Yu's lookalikes)
and Noh Sa Yeon.
- Noh Sa Yeon. - Yes. Also,
I've even been told I look like your mom.
- That's true! - You do.
- You look like her. - I see why.
- I heard that so many times. - I see a resemblance.
- You look similar. - There's a resemblance.
- I did a parody performance... - When she smiles.
(She performed "Good Goodbye" with Lee Chang Ho.)
- There's a resemblance. - of Hwasa's song with Chang Ho.
There was one comment on it...
that said, "How is this a parody of Hwasa?"
(The most-liked comment)
"It's Velvet Dress Ok Jung."
That was the most-liked comment.
- You really look like her. - There's a resemblance.
(She dressed up for the performance.)
- You look similar. - There's a resemblance.
- That's right. - They look so similar.
- They look similar. - When she was younger.
(Velvet Dress Ok Jung is on fire.)
(This comes up when I search for Velvet Dress Ok Jung.)
(Isn't she Haha's mother, Velvet Dress Ok Jung?)
- You look similar. - There's a resemblance.
(That's why Haha especially liked her.)
She looks like her.
There's a resemblance.
- They look alike. - Yes.
(While they're captivated by her charm,)
That's Ju Si Gyung Square right next to us.
(they arrive at their destination, Ju Si Gyung Square.)
- It's this the place? - So this is the place.
- This is the place. - This place is really...
It's really hot in the Ju Si Gyung Square,
(The heat is brutal, so they head straight indoors.)
so we'll head to an indoor space.
You all know what Ju Si Gyung did, right?
(Ju Si Gyung was an independence activist...)
(and a scholar who systematized the Korean language used today.)
- We do. Why wouldn't we? - We know.
- It's common knowledge. - We know.
- What did he do? - What?
- He's the one who... - He...
You know, when we were struggling...
(His poor explanation makes them laugh.)
When we were struggling,
he said, "Look!"
"We're doing this!"
(He seems to be talking about independent activists...)
- We know. - Do what?
(during the Japanese colonial period.)
Isn't it something like that?
Haha. You know it, right?
- Haha knows. - Haha should tell us.
- I know it. - Haha knows.
- Tell us, Haha. - You should...
- explain it to us. - When you think of Ju Si Gyung,
- you think of Korea. - That's right.
- Korea and tears. - That's right.
(His level of knowledge is pretty much the same.)
- He made his mark on history. - That's right, you punks.
- You know him, right? - Hearing his name makes me cry.
He was a Hangul scholar and an independence activist.
(Correct)
- That's right. - Yes, that's right.
- I said "Korea." - Hangul.
(Pretending to know)
I told you.
- Hangul. - He was under Sejong the Great.
- Under? - No.
- He's not from that period. - That's not true.
- During the independence movement. - The independence movement...
- Cut! - He wouldn't have been...
an independence activist under Sejong the Great.
- Please tell us about Ju Si Gyung. - Tell us.
(A brief introduction to Ju Si Gyung)
- Tell us in detail. - Okay.
He was a Korean linguist who devoted himself...
(Listening attentively)
to studying and promoting the Korean language.
He developed Sejong the Great's Hunminjeongeum...
- in the modern form... - I was right.
- of Hangul we use today. - That's right.
Right.
- He made it easier. - That's right.
(He laid the foundation for the Korean alphabet we use today.)
He modernized it.
That's what I was trying to say.
It was a little difficult, so he made it easier...
- That's right. - to read.
What's Hangul?
- Hangul is Korea. - Right.
(Passing by Ju Si Gyung Square that honors his achievements,)
So when you think of Korea,
- you think of Ju Si Gyung. - Okay.
We're really...
(they enter Gwanghwamun, the heart of Seoul.)
This is Gwanghwamun.
- It's really... - There are so many foreigners.
(Impressed)
- Seoul is really... - Ten million people came.
(Many people from other countries came to experience Korean culture.)
Seoul is a global city now.
There are so many foreigners.
They're all foreigners.
(In the heart of global Seoul,)
- Right. - It is a global city.
It became a global city.
(there's another historic place.)
We're here.
That looks nice. We could get a cup of coffee.
(Sejong Center for the Performing Arts)
(A multi-purpose arts center that opened in 1987,)
That's pretty.
(featuring a variety of exhibitions and performances)
What are we going to do now?
(Excited)
"Because the language of this country..."
- "is different from that of China," - "Different from that of China."
(The preface to Hunminjeongeum catches their eye.)
"it doesn't correspond with Chinese characters."
- No way. - Thus, the people...
(Hangul is everywhere in this place.)
Instead of Ju Si Gyung Square,
you've arrived at the Story of King Sejong...
and Chungmugong Admiral Yi Sun Sin Exhibition Halls.
We're at the Sejong Center.
(The Story of King Sejong and Chungmugong Admiral Yi Sun Sin)
- This is incredible. - Right?
(A hands-on exhibition where visitors can experience...)
There's even a royal robe.
(the lives of King Sejong and Admiral Yi Sun Sin)
He's a legend.
We are Korea.
The game you'll play here...
(A mission they'll carry out in a place filled with history)
is Cone Hat Waiter.
(Mission 2: Cone Hat Waiter)
- Cone Hat Waiter? - Cone hat?
One person will sit...
- with a container on their head. - Right.
The other person, wearing a cone hat over their eyes,
has to walk over and pour water into it.
The team that collects...
the most water in 80 seconds wins.
We'll begin with Team Jong Kook.
Do we go first? Got it.
- Does this limit your view? - Seok Sam, good luck.
(How much water will Team Jong Kook be able to move?)
We've got this.
- It won't be that hard. - Is that necessary?
(Seok Sam, the oldest, will take water.)
- He'll be taking a shower. - What?
(The others put on cone hats.)
I can't see a thing.
- I doubt you can see a thing. - No way.
(They have to see through this hole.)
Guys.
- Don't pretend you can't see. - I can't see a thing!
(POV)
Seriously, we can't see anything.
Just don't pretend you can't see.
- I see clearly. - Got it?
- I'm fine. - Jong Kook can see.
(Perfect size for him)
Having small eyes actually helps me see perfectly.
Really? Okay, let's do this for real.
Go, team!
- Line up Seok Jin's face... - Yes?
(Strategy)
through this opening as you walk toward him.
- That's it. - Line up his face?
Haha, you're up first. Get ready.
(Haha from Team Jong Kook will go first.)
- Just a second. - Get ready.
Haha, let's do this!
- Get ready. - Okay, go.
(80-second countdown starts.)
- Go on. - Take your time.
- You can't touch him. - Aren't we allowed to talk?
(Striding)
- Yes, keep going. - What?
- You can talk. - You're close enough now.
- You've come as far as you need to. - You can't touch him.
(He pauses as Seok Sam says.)
Do your best and take your time.
- Nice. - Looking good.
- He's doing great. - Good job.
I'm dead serious right now.
Take it more seriously!
Wait. It's running down the side.
(Pouring like a waterfall)
- Haha, this is wrong. Just wrong. - Nicely done.
- A little to the side, Haha. - Haha...
(Flicking)
- Where did you poke him? - Where did you just poke him?
- A little to the side, Haha. - Haha...
Where did you just poke him?
Are you kidding me?
(Laughing)
Sorry about that.
That really hurts.
- Hurry up! - We're on the clock.
No, that's not necessary.
- Hurry up! - Hurry up. You have limited time.
(He pours in the water after hearing they're short on time.)
No, that's not necessary.
- Hurry! - No, take your time.
- Jong Kook, you're next! - Sure.
- Hey, I did great. - Let me see.
Nice!
(The bottle is still half full.)
Okay, just go.
- Nice! - Okay, just go.
(Small Eyes is next.)
You can't peek.
- Hold still. - Take your time.
(Assertive)
- The clock's ticking. - You've got this.
Judging from how Haha did...
(He sees through the small hole with his small eyes.)
- It can't touch the other bottle. - Don't let them touch.
(Target locked in)
Nice.
(Pinpoint accuracy)
No way.
- No way. - He'll fill the whole bottle.
He'll fill the whole bottle at this rate.
(It's almost done.)
Hey, the bottle's almost full.
Hey, it's running down.
(Pouring out his bottle and filling Seok Jin's)
- Okay. - Nicely done.
(Team Jong Kook is on a roll, and it's Ji Hyo's turn.)
- Go. - We'll swap bottles.
The clock is ticking.
(Switching to a new bottle)
- We're beasts at this. - Look at us go!
- Ji Yu, wait. Hold on. - You're in the perfect spot.
- Look at how she does it. - Ji Yu, you're in the perfect spot.
- That's the spot. - You took too long.
(Getting close)
- You can't touch each other. - Seriously.
- That's the spot. - You're in the perfect place.
(Confused)
- Right there. - Start pouring.
- Ji Yu, go ahead. - Speed things up, will you?
(Pouring)
Pour all the water.
- Just give up! - Your aim is off.
(She rushes back after drenching Seok Jin.)
We still have Ji Hyo left.
(In a rush)
Hold on. How much time do we have left?
- Just go. - You have 20 seconds left.
(They have 20 seconds left, and Ji Yu sets off.)
- It's Ji Yu. - I can't see a thing.
- Ji Yu! - Ji Yu's up.
(Making a fuss)
- Ji Yu, not there! - Keep pouring.
More!
- Where's the bottle? - Ji Yu!
- You have 15 seconds left. - Hold on.
- Fifteen seconds. - Wait.
- Ji Yu! - Where's his head?
- Aim properly. No, not there. - Eight, seven,
(Pouring right in his face)
- Pour everything in. - six, five, four,
(She used all the water to wash his face.)
- I emptied the bottle. - three, two,
- I couldn't see a thing. - one.
I couldn't see anything.
- What did she even do? - Seok Sam's party is over.
(Team Jong Kook is done.)
- Look at him. - Are you kidding me?
- Oh no. - Get over here, guys.
(Ji Hyo and Ji Yu)
I'm really sorry, but I couldn't see anything.
(Just a little bit of water)
- Ji Hyo, get over here. - They got a lot.
- That's not it. - I tried my best.
(Sorry)
I could see my own bottle but not yours.
It was pretty obvious.
- You didn't try that hard. - I mean...
(While the old man, completely drenched, is scolding them,)
- I did. - I really did.
- I just couldn't see it. - I couldn't see anything.
- This is harder than it seems. - Here's what I saw.
(the members of Team Jae Seok put on cone hats.)
You just walked straight toward him.
You guys had the luxury of taking your time.
- They weren't kidding about this! - Still, you...
I can't see a thing.
(They're amazed by how little they can see through the hole.)
- I can't see anything. - We were rushed.
You really can't see anything?
(Jin Ho takes a seat to take water.)
I really can't see anything. I thought they were joking.
The one who does the best can go twice.
(With 3 members, Team Jae Seok gets 2 attempts per person.)
Couldn't Ji Hyo have done it?
Look through the cone hat...
and line up your sight with the bottle.
(Confident)
- You'll go twice. - I'll bend down...
and point the bottle at an angle.
(Strategy)
Get ready, and...
(Their 80 seconds start now.)
- Off he goes. - All right.
- You can see me, right? - We really can't.
- In the center... Okay. - You're on limited time.
Hurry up.
(Jae Seok's in front of him in an instant.)
I think you're in a good spot.
- Right? - It seems perfect.
I really can't see a thing.
- You're doing great. - You really can't see the bottle.
(Relating)
He can't see that well without his glasses too.
Give it a test run.
- Jae Seok, I... - Look at that.
(Gibberish)
Who's that?
(Not even close)
- Look at him go. - He's so good at this.
- No way. - Seriously?
- How am I doing? - Move it back a little.
No, forward. Toward you.
(Going back and forth)
Jae Seok, toward your chest.
- Jae Seok... - Toward you.
(He completely missed the target.)
More!
Jin Ho, place your bottle under his.
- That's cheating. - Place it under his.
(Getting even farther)
- Oh no. - A little more.
- A little to the right. - No, not that way.
(He's so good at avoiding water.)
Jin Ho, tilt yours forward.
- No way. - Jin Ho's terrible at this.
- What? - Seriously.
- I agree. - How is he so bad at this?
(Shaking)
I don't think...
(He goes back after washing Jin Ho's hair.)
- we got a lot. - I couldn't aim straight.
- Jin Ho shouldn't do that. - I couldn't aim properly.
(Only a small amount)
- Are you kidding me? - Seriously.
- Jin Ho's so bad at this. - He's terrible at this.
All I did was sit here!
(Lie)
- Let it pour down the front. - Good job, Ye Eun.
(Ye Eun is struggling as well.)
- Good going. - You should get it in the bottle.
- Go for it. - They're running out of time.
(He begins washing his face.)
Ye Eun, forward.
Forward. A little more.
Up!
- No, not there. - More.
- To the left! - Can they guide...
- each other like this? - A little to the back.
(Jae Seok is controlling Ddochi, his avatar.)
- Yes, right there! - That shouldn't be allowed.
Ye Eun, a little to the back.
(She just has to pour the water like that.)
- To the back. - Forward.
(He guides her the wrong way with his eyes shut.)
- Forward. - Jin Ho, tell her yourself.
- Ye Eun, to the right. - Jin Ho, open your eyes!
Then water will get in my eyes.
That's so cold!
(The former professional gamer is so bad at this game.)
- I can't believe him. - Unbelievable.
We've lost. He's terrible at this.
- Forward. - We've won.
- Good job. - I meant toward you.
(Ye Eun also fails and goes back.)
- Unbelievable. - I couldn't see a thing.
(Ssaebssaeb goes next.)
- Go ahead. - Look at Se Chan go.
He looks determined.
- I... - Wait. Hold up the bottle.
(Clenching his teeth)
(He slowly adjusts the zero.)
- Se Chan! - A little forward.
(Accurate!)
- Isn't this it? - Yes.
- I can feel it getting heavier. - He's doing it.
- No way. Look at him go. - Up a little.
(If he pours all the water into the bottle,)
(they'll catch up with Team Jong Kook.)
Stay right there.
- Up a little. - Look at him go.
(Staggering)
What...
Jin Ho keeps dodging out of the way.
- You shouldn't move. - Jin Ho, why are you moving?
(Shaking)
- No, not there. - You shouldn't move.
- He keeps dodging out of the way. - Aim for the bottle yourself!
Aim for the bottle yourself!
- He's terrible at this. - He keeps dodging out of the way.
Twenty seconds.
- Hold up the bottle. - Twenty seconds.
(20 seconds are left, and Jae Seok tries again.)
- Hold it up. - Hold it up.
- Where is it? - Unbelievable.
(If Jae Seok pours all the water into the bottle, they'll tie!)
Jae Seok, give it a test.
Even without the cone hat, Jae Seok can't see clearly.
(Will he be able to pour it properly?)
Jin Ho, where's the bottle?
- Right there. - Jae Seok can't see clearly.
- Where is it? - Just give it a test.
- Seven, six... - Jae Seok, looking good.
A little bit forward.
- Forward. - Nice.
- Four. - Four.
- Three. - Jae Seok, just pour all of it.
- Two. - A little bit more forward.
- One. - Toward you, Jae Seok.
(Time is up.)
- Keep pouring. - Okay!
(Miserable)
- Game over. - It's over.
- Why is he so bad at this? - Okay, nice!
- No way. - You see,
(He starts making an excuse.)
I couldn't see where it was, so I couldn't guide you.
Also, even though I said forward,
you pushed it more toward me.
I didn't get anything you just said.
Clean out your ears, then.
Clean my ears out?
(King Sejong will get mad at him for his pronunciation.)
It's impossible to communicate with him.
How can we win when he can't speak Korean?
Okay, good.
(Team Jong Kook, Team Jae Seok)
- This wasn't easy. - It was a tough game.
Team Jong Kook wins this game.
- Nice! - We completely crushed them.
- Unbelievable. - Come on.
The winning team gets two balls per person.
- Okay! - Nice.
- Here you go. - Right.
Of course we'll go for the prize.
Team Jae Seok gets one per person.
(Team Jae Seok, the losing team, gets 1 name ball each.)
- Good job. - That was a close one.
- We could've won. - Let's go for the prize.
- Sure thing. - Just take a look at me.
- Sure. - Absolutely.
(He argues that he got soaked for the team.)
- Okay, you get credit for that. - You totally deserve it.
I should write my own name down, of course.
(Kim Jong Kook)
(Everyone writes their own name on the balls put into the prize box.)
- Hey. - Hey.
- There was nothing we could do. - Wasn't it an accident?
(Glancing)
I have two.
- Hey, wait. - Be careful.
(Kim Ji Yu, Jee Seok Jin)
- Sorry about that. - Seok Jin.
- I really didn't know. - Do people make mistakes like that?
(Seok Jin's name goes on one of her balls?)
All day, I...
(Penalty box, Prize box)
(She puts Seok Jin's name into the penalty box once again.)
Did you put all of yours in the prize box?
One in the prize box...
- and one in the penalty box. - Really?
(She only goes after Seok Jin.)
I made a promise, you see.
- With the team. - Okay.
(Meanwhile, the members of Team Jae Seok got 1 ball each.)
Are you going for the prize?
- Of course. - The prize?
- Yes, the prize. - Do you mean that?
(Without a word)
Our team hasn't landed on a penalty space yet.
(Hong Jin Ho, can't communicate)
Oh, I see.
You can only write the names of your teammates.
Just a friendly reminder.
- I wouldn't put it anywhere else. - Are you sure?
(In the penalty box)
Are you sure?
Is it going in the penalty box or the prize box?
(Spotting Ssaebssaeb)
Why you little...
(Getting back at Se Chan right away)
I'm going to watch you guys.
(Se Chan gets another penalty ball.)
I really put mine in the prize box.
- Earlier, I... - Seriously?
(Jae Seok writes down Ye Eun's name again.)
(Playing tricks with his hands again)
I'm going to smash this if you play games with me.
(Another penalty ball for Ye Eun)
(Now that the session of betrayal and payback is over,)
Now you get to roll again.
(it's time to roll the dice again.)
- The die. - Give us the die.
(Team Jae Seok will throw it first.)
Okay, Ssaebssaeb will roll.
Since I'm already up, I'll roll it.
What's a good number for us?
- Six? - If you think about it...
- The bigger, the better. - We need a six.
Roll a six.
- Six gets us to a restaurant. - Six.
- Four or six. - Four or six.
- Four. - Four or six.
- Roll a 4. - Anything but a 5.
- Sure. - Four or six.
(Penalty: Jogyesa Temple)
Anything but a five.
- Okay, here I go. - Go ahead.
(Team Jae Seok rolls the die.)
Four or six. Any even number.
- Any even number. - Nice.
- Let it be a four. - Nice.
- A four. - I'm getting a good feeling.
- What? - Four!
(4 or 6 is good. Anything but a 5!)
- Four or six. - Four.
Anything but a five.
- What? - Four!
- Five? - Five isn't good.
- What's that? - It's a penalty space.
- Five. - It's a penalty space.
- A penalty space? - One, two, three, four, five.
(Jogyesa Temple, a penalty space!)
- Yes! - Nice!
- So long, Seok Jin. - Team Jae Seok lands...
(Sighing)
- on a penalty space. - Nice going.
- What do we need to roll? - I'm sorry.
- Let's go to a restaurant. - Let's all write his name.
(Write Se Chan's name on the penalty ball.)
Since he got us there, let's write down his name.
- What do we need to roll? - He should receive the penalty.
- Of course. - Let's see.
- His name should be drawn. - One...
(Team Jong Kook goes next.)
What do we need to roll?
- One isn't so bad. - A four.
- One and four. - One and four.
(Golden Key)
(Prize: Ju Si Gyung Square)
I can't believe you.
- One or four. - One and four are good.
- What shouldn't we roll? - What's bad for us?
- Two. - Two.
(Penalty: Memorial Hall)
We should avoid the island too.
(Deserted Island)
Two and...
- Five. - Two.
- Two and five. - Anything but two and five.
Two and five are bad. One and four are good.
Okay. Anything but 2 and 5.
- What about 2 and 5? - That's no good.
I expect a 2 or 5.
- Two or five. - Two or five.
(Mad)
Two or five.
- What? - Why are you fuming?
One or four.
You're annoying me.
(He's always ready to get mad.)
It's okay to comment.
- Two or five. - Where are you going, mister?
- Two. - Two.
(Bouncing the dice off his head)
- It's a 2. - It's a 2!
(What's the result?)
It's a two.
Five!
- What's the five? - Two or five.
- Deserted Island. - Deserted Island.
Deserted Island.
(Deserted Island)
(They land on the Deserted Island.)
It's a bad thing.
Why did you take us to the Deserted Island?
(Blaming)
- Why bounce it off a head? - Why did you do that?
(This is what he gets for being mean.)
It could be a good thing.
(Trying to stay optimistic)
- Do they really go? - It could be good.
(They reveal what the Deserted Island is.)
- You landed on the Deserted Island. - It could be good.
You must skip a turn and also complete a mission.
Team Jong Kook must find a location where there are no people,
and must not meet a single soul for five minutes.
- That's hard. - That's the worst.
(Sejong Center at lunchtime on a weekday)
- That's not easy. - Is there such a place?
(Is that doable?)
- We can manage. - For five minutes?
I'm good at finding such places because we're Running Man.
- They can't find us. - You're built different.
(Is she impressed?)
- You get three tries. - That's funny.
If you fail three times, you each get a penalty ball.
- Okay. - And if we succeed?
- Then you escape. - We escape.
- We escape. - If we succeed.
We're good at going unnoticed.
We just need to find a good spot.
I go unnoticed at home for six hours at a time.
Even when you're with your wife?
- Your wife's ignoring you. - Is that it?
Team Jong Kook shall set off now.
- Okay. - Let's go.
(They set off with the hide-and-seek master.)
Where should we go?
It's lunchtime.
(Deserted Island Mission: Don't bump into anyone for 5 minutes.)
How can we last five minutes without meeting anyone at lunchtime?
Not getting noticed... That's difficult.
(They head above ground first.)
We can do this.
Five minutes is longer than you think.
We can't pull that off anywhere nearby.
(Worried)
- This mission... - Five minutes...
We can do it. I'll show you, Ji Yu. This is possible...
because...
- This is Running Man. - Yes.
- Right. - You saw earlier.
(Ji Yu already learned from him.)
- Yes. I was so surprised. - Right?
Gosh, look. I can see 100 people from right here.
(They got to the 1st floor.)
- We must go to a corner. - It's too crowded.
Does that even make sense?
(But there are so many people!)
- This place... - Everyone's staring.
It's lunchtime and there are at least 100 people here.
(At a glance)
There are too many people.
(On top of that, Ji Yu, the YouTube star, is with them.)
It'll get even more crowded.
Later on...
It's more crowded than before.
- Let's go outside. - Outside?
- We must go outside. - Look for other places?
(They have no choice but to go outside.)
- Outside... - Other spots...
In some corner...
- We can't hide under a car, right? - That's best.
- How about that ATM box? - Five minutes...
Would people stay away that long?
(With an open view on all sides,)
We just need no one to come in for five minutes.
(it looks like a tough place to complete the mission.)
Do we have to stay out of sight or do they just not have to ID us?
- The second floor... - They can't recognize you.
(Writer: "They can't recognize you.")
- If they see us? - If they see us?
They can't even go, "hey?"
That means they recognized you.
(Writer: "That means they recognized you.")
We can't be recognized.
(They must hide in the open.)
- Back there. - Up these stairs...
(If anyone spots them within 5 minutes, they fail the mission.)
- Jong Kook. The second floor. - Back there.
This works? Let's have a look.
(They go up the stairs.)
- Nice. It's quiet. - This place works.
(Empty)
- This place works. - For five minutes.
- There are no people. - Is it cool?
This is a good spot. It's the only spot.
Go into the alley on the left.
- Get in there. - This is the spot.
(This is the spot Seok Sam was talking about.)
- Get in there. - This is it.
Go inside. This is the spot.
Gosh, it's hot.
We have no choice.
- This is great. - Isn't it?
(Current temperature: 36°C)
- If we crouch... - This might work.
(It's hot, but it's a perfect spot.)
Turn around. Face the wall.
We chose our spot.
- We'll start the timer. - Okay.
- You can't stand around. - Get lost.
- Film from a distance. - Go really far away.
(They even snap at the staff members, telling them to hide.)
- Walk away. - In here...
- Come here. - All of you.
- Cameramen. - Gather round.
Hide your name tags.
(They huddle together in a corner like a family of cockroaches.)
We just have to avoid making eye contact. It's fine.
That's right.
(It's scorching hot, and the 5-minute countdown begins.)
This is it.
- Let's film like this. - Okay.
The camera's down here.
(They're hiding here.)
No one will find us here.
Anyone who looks is creepy.
(Will no one find them for 5 minutes?)
We have to hunch around like this.
I like this angle. A pre-fight shot.
This angle...
Ji Yu. Why do you think this will succeed?
What? Because this is Running Man.
- That's right. - This is Running Man.
Everyone here is an expert.
Would we lose to an idol?
- No, never. - Why not?
- Because you're Running Man. - Yes.
(Is she brainwashed?)
For real.
- No. - Out of your friends,
- the stronger ones. - I know a few.
Do you think they can rip Seok Jin's name tag?
- They can't. - No, right?
- Why not? - I can bet 1,000 dollars.
Do you know why?
I got it, okay?
- I feel it. - You said it a few times.
(Ji Yu is tired of playing along.)
I got it so well already.
(They chat to kill time.)
- You said it a few times. - I got it so well already.
- No one will come by. - Passers-by...
(Right then)
- Wait. - No one would come here.
(Two people enter the place.)
- Why would they? - Passing by...
No one has any business coming here.
(Glancing)
(They looked?)
- They're gone. - They might want to look.
(Zooming by)
No...
(They went by!)
Someone went by, but they looked straight ahead.
- Isn't that good? - They don't look this way.
Rip it off and see what happens.
(Removing his name tag just in case)
- They won't... - They went by.
Someone else walked by, but they looked the other way.
- This is Running Man. - Yes.
(She says it without being told now.)
We're bound to succeed.
(3 minutes have already passed.)
- Anyone who looks is a freak. - Yes.
This is where bullies take your money.
Yes, it is. I lost some cash that way.
- This place... - Older schoolgirls...
- drag you here by your arms. - Yes.
- When strangers see you, - Pretending to be friends.
(Ji Yu tells them how she got robbed.)
- they'd think you're friends. - Yes.
- "Come with us." - And then?
They take your cash in a dark corner.
What if you give up your money?
(Just 1 minute and 15 seconds more, and they'll succeed!)
- They bring you here for the cash. - Yes.
They change as soon as they reach the dark corner.
Totally.
Do they ask how much you have?
(Just then)
No, they...
Do they ask how much you have?
- No, they... - Hey.
- I just... - You handed it over?
(He recognized the members!)
They snatched it. In elementary school,
some middle-school girls...
You failed to escape with one minute to go.
- What? - Why?
A passer-by saw you and went "hey."
- No way. - You're lying.
(They resist first.)
We didn't see anyone.
They can't even go, "hey?"
- That means they recognized you. - We can't be recognized.
(He broke the rule...)
(that Seok Sam confirmed exactly.)
With just one minute to go...
(There's only 1 minute left, but they failed!)
You have two chances left.
(Team Jong Kook failed on their first attempt.)
Somewhere else?
Isn't this the best spot?
It's too much pressure.
(Meanwhile, Team Jae Seok is trying something.)
- Let's go! - One, two, three.
- Let's go! - Let's go.
(Cards?)
- This stack... - We'll have leftovers.
(Team Jae Seok got a bonus mission.)
When Jin Ho was on last time, we played a board game...
(It's the pronunciation game Jin Ho played last time.)
where you had to read tongue-twisters quickly.
Downtown sushi restaurant. The Great...
(Downtown sushi restaurant, The Great Dharani Sutra)
(Each time you fail, you must draw another card.)
- "Great." - Take your time.
Downtown sushi restaurant.
(The Great Dharani Sutra)
The Great Deer...
Everyone must read every card successfully in 30 seconds.
- All these? - All these?
You get three blank balls.
- Okay. One, two, three. - Let's go!
(Jin Ho goes first.)
- Ready? - We'll have leftovers.
Ready?
Seventieth birthday party at home.
(Surprisingly, he succeeds!)
To defame and then praise.
(Se Chan also makes it!)
Seventieth blirthday...
Start over quick. Flip a card.
Seventieth birthday party at home.
To defame and then praise.
Nutritious red bean jelly.
- Nice. - You pass.
(Ye Eun makes it!)
(If Jae Seok reads it, they'll succeed!)
Seventieth birthday party at home.
To defame and then praise.
Nutritious red bean jelly.
Sitting in groups with twinkling eyes.
Okay!
- Okay! - You succeeded!
(They pull off a dramatic victory with just 1 second left!)
- Great. - You get three blank balls.
- Three? - Yes.
- Prize... - We go all-in for a prize.
- Of course. - We must get a prize.
Let's go for a prize.
One person doesn't get one.
(Writer: "One person doesn't get one.")
- What? - Someone doesn't get one.
(There are 4 people and 3 balls.)
- Why not? - Then...
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Ready or not...
- Ready or not... - No.
Let's play the cards.
- The cards. - The cards.
The cards?
- I'll lose, then. - Flip cards?
The order is important too.
(Individual battle for the ball)
Jae Seok, we can't say each syllable...
- slowly or... - That's not fair.
(They can't pause in the middle of a word.)
We must read it smoothly.
We have to read just one, right?
(The moment they make it, they'll receive a ball.)
We take turns and if we pass, we take a ball.
- Rock-paper-scissors? - For the order.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(They play rock-paper-scissors to decide the order.)
- Okay. - Rock-paper-scissors.
- I'll go first. - I'll go second.
(Order: Se Chan, Ye Eun, Jin Ho, Jae Seok)
- It's best to go first. - One, two, three, four.
- One, two, three. - We start right away.
Let's all succeed so Jae Seok looses out.
(Se Chan goes first.)
- Ready? - Wait.
A, E, I, O, U.
- Gwanghwamun Square. - Read it fast.
Ready, go.
(Red bean and kidney bean porridge)
Red. Bean. And. Kidney. Bean. Porridge.
- You're out. - Why?
- You... - You separated the syllables.
(Se Chan forgot the rule he made.)
- Oh, right, okay. - You're out.
- I should say it quick? - Try again.
(They let it slide once.)
- Ready? - Count me in.
- One, two... - Staccato reading is banned.
(Writer: "Staccato reading is banned!")
- One, two, three. - What's "staccato?"
(Sodium perrhenate)
Sodium perrhen...
(Incorrect)
- You're out. - I got stuck.
(Se Chan fails.)
- It's hard. - It's hard.
(Next is Ye Eun.)
- It's still on. - This is nerve-racking.
(Balanced appointment policy)
Balanced apinment policy.
- Incorrect. - You said "apinment."
(Incorrect)
(Kong Jin Ho's turn)
- Okay, my turn. - I'm annoyed.
(Law of photochemical equivalence)
Loo of phitochemical eqeevalence.
(Incorrect)
Forget it.
(Does he think it's unfair?)
- I said it. - Forget it.
- You failed. - I said it.
It didn't sound like a word.
(He failed because he just barked.)
You can't force it.
(It's Jae Seok's turn.)
Ready?
- Don't pause. One, two, three. - Go.
(Caesar's seezle deezle's seezle)
Caesar's seezle deezle seezle.
- What was that? - "Deezle seezle."
(Everyone failed once.)
- Cards, please. - Start over.
How about we try this?
Blah-blah-blah, blah-blah-blah.
- That much... - Let's allow that.
(They can take their time and read the word with a rhythm.)
- That's fine. - Okay.
A bit of a rhythm.
- Ssaebssaeb - Blah-blah.
(Se Chan goes first.)
- A bit of a rhythm. - Take your time.
- A slight rhythm is fine. - Ready, go.
Law of photochemical equivalence.
That's fine for now.
- Wasn't that okay? - It was.
(It was not perfect, but he gets a pass.)
- Objectively. - It wasn't bad.
If that's a no, everything else is a no.
(Next up is Ye Eun.)
- Next. - Good luck.
Kwak Jin Gwang tourism manager.
- That was... - That was...
(Ye Eun also gets a pass.)
- You can't... - I aced it.
(There's one ball left, and it's Jin Ho's turn!)
- You're next. - Okay.
You can go slow.
- I'll add a rhythm. - One, two, three.
(One single-use ticket per person per day)
- I'll add a rhythm. - You can go slow.
One, two, three.
One one one one... Okay.
One one one one...
Okay.
(A creative way to read a tongue-twister)
Jin Ho, were you lagging?
One one one one...
(Shaking)
- What does that mean? - What is this word?
(There's one ball left, and it's Jae Seok's turn.)
Is this kind of rhythm allowed?
- Yes. - Okay.
(Rolling his tongue)
In the meantime...
(A loud warm-up for the eyes and ears)
What are you doing? Here you go.
One, two, three.
Balanced appointment policy.
- That was too... - Wait.
- You took too long. - That was fine. It was precise.
(They think he was a bit slow.)
- There was buffering. - It was precise.
- While you did it correctly... - I did it correctly, right?
- Let's give Jin Ho another shot. - Okay.
(Alternative)
- Give it a shot. - This is your last chance.
(If Jin Ho makes it this time, he'll compete against Jae Seok again.)
- Let's see if you succeed in it. - Okay.
- If I win, I'll get a ball. - Yes, we promise.
(The last chance for the master)
- This is your last chance. - Give me a good one.
Your last chance.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
(One single-use ticket per person per day)
One one one one...
- Hey. - Why do I keep getting that one?
- You picked it on purpose, right? - "One one..."
(Jin Ho thinks it's unfair.)
- Incorrect. - Okay.
We'll put them in the prize box. Don't worry.
(Se Chan, Ye Eun, and Jae Seok receives 1 empty ball each.)
- We'll put them in the prize box. - Exactly.
One...
(While Jin Ho studies,)
One single-use...
We'll put them in the prize box this time.
There is no way they'll see us...
(Team Jong Kook hides again.)
- here. - There is no way.
- We could film short-form videos. - We're set.
(Here)
- I'm serious. - We'll succeed in it.
(They're perfectly hidden, and 4 minutes and 20 seconds have passed.)
- We'll succeed in it. - No one will enter.
Kids might enter.
- Right. Kids might do that. - "What are those?"
- They'll come for the characters. - Five and six-year-olds.
(Larva)
- That's right. - We could mouth words.
- "Go away." - That's right.
We can pretend to be Larva characters.
(Hiding as Larva characters)
- If people pass by... - They won't see us.
(At that moment)
What if someone opens this door and walks out?
- No way. - It'll be unbelievable.
If people come here to take photos...
(One man goes toward the members.)
No way.
The stairs.
- You must be lying. No. - Don't look.
(Did he pass by?)
(Walking)
- Is someone coming? - You must be lying.
- The footsteps are getting closer. - No way.
(Will they get found with 10 seconds remaining?)
(What will happen?)
Don't look.
- You escaped the deserted island. - Okay.
- Okay. - Okay.
(Thankfully, the gentleman passed by!)
- You must be lying. No. - What's this sound? Don't look.
- You escaped the deserted island. - Okay.
(Nice!)
- Okay. - Okay.
See? We succeeded in it.
(They did it on their 2nd attempt.)
- Okay. - All right.
- It was a good spot. - Had we failed again...
(Proud)
- It was a good spot. - Running Man doesn't disappoint.
- I'm glad we didn't give up. - I know.
- We succeeded in it. - Ji Yu.
(Here he goes again.)
Say it yourself.
Say it to the camera.
Why did we succeed in it?
It's because...
we're Running Man.
(Satisfied)
Correct.
They'll never guess that we've succeeded in it.
(With the power of Running Man, they leave the Deserted Island...)
This is nice.
(and head toward Jogyesa Temple, their destination!)
- Let's go to the Jogyesa Temple. - Okay.
So this is how it looks.
(The second spot Team Jae Seok arrived at)
It's really cool.
Team Jae Seok has arrived...
- at the Jogyesa Temple. - Jogyesa Temple.
Jogyesa Temple is the first Buddhist temple...
(Jogyesa Temple: The first Buddhist temple built...)
- to be built within the four gates. - Really?
(within Seoul's Four Inner Gates)
It's also the first Buddhist temple in Korea...
that was built in the city for missionary work.
Avalokitesvara Bodhisattva.
- Avalokitesvara Bodhisattva. - They're having a lotus festival,
(Nestled peacefully among the skyscrapers of Jongno,)
so look around...
- Okay. - and hang up a lantern if you want.
(Jogyesa Temple hosts its annual Lotus Flower Festival every summer.)
Then you'll gather around, roll the dice,
- and move to a new location. - Okay.
It's so pretty.
How pretty.
These lanterns are for good health and good fortune.
(The colorful lotus lanterns contain different wishes.)
The lanterns make a sound...
when the wind blows.
- My goodness. - Is that an actual flower?
Yes, it is. Isn't it beautiful?
- The color is no joke. - I know.
(In the height of summer, lotus flowers fill the temple with color.)
It's so pretty.
- The wind makes them chime. - It's nice.
- They made this place beautiful. - How nice.
(The temple ASMR puts their minds at peace.)
How nice.
It's pretty, right?
It's pretty.
- Someone wished to get into SBS. - What?
- Where is it? - No way.
(They spot a wish they're happy to see.)
You're right.
(I hope I get accepted by SBS.)
I hope they get in.
Seok Sam, did you write a wish?
- Yes. - You should do it too, Jae Seok.
- You should write something. - Of course.
(Wishing lanterns are the highlights of the lotus festival.)
- I'll hang up a lantern too. - Okay.
(He writes each letter with care.)
- Ji Hyo, did you write it? - Yes.
(They attach their wishes to the lotus lanterns.)
This place puts my mind at peace.
I love the sound.
Look.
(Jae Seok's wish)
"I wish for our health and peaceful lives."
I wish for them as well.
(I wish for our health and peaceful lives.)
I made that wish for all of us.
Seok Jin, did you wish for the stock prices to rise?
(Laughing sadly)
- I bet you did. - I wouldn't do that.
My goodness.
My family's happiness and health are...
all I care about. The stock prices don't matter.
(The stock prices don't matter.)
(Seok Jin wrote his wish with a gloomy expression.)
Listen to this sound.
It sounds so mysterious.
"I wish for happiness..."
"of my family members and everyone I know."
(I wish for happiness...)
(of my family members and everyone I know.)
I want them to receive good energy as they come in.
(Se Chan, who wants to receive good energy, makes a wish.)
"Health and blessing for everyone in the Running Man crew!"
(They hope their beloved ones will become happier!)
"Please help everyone make a lot of money."
It'll be nice to eat. This time,
(They feel hungry after making wishes.)
we're competing to eat.
We need to get on that square.
- Anything will work. I'm hungry. - I can't wait to eat.
- I want pork gukbap. - Same here.
- I want pork gukbap. - Pork gukbap sounds good.
- Sundae gukbap will be better. - Se Chan.
Pork gukbap will be better.
You like pork gukbap because you're a pig, right?
(Childish)
That's right.
(Annoyed)
- We can't get gukbap. - Temple food.
(We can't get gukbap.)
Why not? Which number do we need?
We need five for temple food.
(Team Jong Kook will land on temple food only.)
That sounds nice. Getting five isn't impossible.
Gukbap is two squares after that one.
(They can't get gukbap this turn.)
- But Team Jae Seok has... - We might get that square.
(On the other hand, Team Jae Seok has 2 restaurant options.)
- Which number do they need? - One or...
- Do they have two options? - They have...
- one more option. - Do they have one more option?
It won't be easy for you to eat.
(Team Jong Kook)
Where... Where can we go?
- Which number do we need? - We need five.
(They need to roll a 5 to have lunch...)
- Five. - We have a good chance.
- Do we need five? - One or...
(since they can't get gukbap.)
- Two, three. - We need five.
If we get the Golden Key,
(If they roll a 3, they'll get the Golden Key.)
- we'll get another chance. - Yes, you're right.
Please.
We really need to eat now.
(Desperate)
- Jae Seok, we have a good chance. - We need five.
(If Team Jae Seok rolls a 3, they'll get gukbap!)
- Three. - We need five.
- It'll be great if we get 3. - Not 4.
(They can't roll a 4 or 5 to avoid the penalty or Deserted Island.)
- We need 3. - We can't get 5 or 4.
- Five or four. - They need five.
- Please. - Who will roll the die?
- Go ahead. - Shall I roll the die?
(Team Jae Seok rolls the dice first.)
- Jae Seok, please get us gukbap. - Where is Ji Hyo?
One or three.
(1: Golden Key, 2: Prize, 3: Penalty, 4: Deserted Island)
- Four or five. - Four or five.
Five or four.
(Attracting bad energy)
- Four or five. - Four or five.
(He bows to the Buddha statue.)
- Three. - Please accept our offerings.
- One or three. - One or three.
- Three. - Four or five.
(Team Jae Seok's lunch...)
- One or three. - One or three.
- One or three. - Four.
(depends on this die of fate!)
- Please. - Five.
- One or three. - Four.
(Will Team Jae Seok get a 3 as they want?)
Four.
One or three.
- Three. - Three.
(It's a 3!)
- Yes! - Are you serious?
You're the best. This is insane.
(The unlucky member, Jae Seok gets them gukbap right away!)
This is insane.
- Hey. - Jae Seok.
Thank you.
(Thank you, Buddha.)
Please listen to our prayer.
- They'll eat gukbap. - This is insane.
- Really? - Hey.
(They can't believe the miracle the unlucky guy just pulled off.)
This is insane.
- I can't believe it. - Jae Seok.
Thank you.
(He got a boost from the temple's good vibes and got a lucky number.)
- This is incredible. - This is insane.
Seriously.
- You know... - This is insane.
- Seriously. - I wanted to eat gukbap.
Seriously, Buddha helped me.
- He helped us eat gukbap. - I know.
Team Jae Seok can eat.
(Team Jae Seok lands on the gukbap space.)
Okay.
- All right. - Buddha...
- Buddha can't read the room. - This is insane.
Ji Hyo and I...
- We're actual Buddhists. - We've donated a lot of money...
(These two Buddhist devotees donated quite a few roof tiles.)
- to the temples. - We've donated a lot of money.
Ji Hyo, roll the die.
We should pray too.
Hey, three or five.
(The hungry believers wish for good luck.)
Buddha, we're hungry.
Three for the Golden Key or five.
(3: Golden Key, 5: Prize, 4: Penalty)
- If we don't get 3 or 5... - Let's eat. Any food will do.
- Please. - Buddha.
- We just need five. - Any food...
Any food will do.
- Buddha won't grant two wishes. - All right.
(Buddha won't grant 2 wishes.)
- One, two... - Buddha won't grant two wishes.
- One, two, - Avalokitesvara Bodhisattva.
- three. - Please.
(The die leaves Buddhist Song's hands.)
- Three. - Please.
- Three or five. - You keep...
They'll fail.
(Will Buddha grant this team's wish as well?)
Three or five.
- You keep... - Three.
(Team Jong Kook got a 3.)
- It's three. - Three is nice.
(They got the Golden Key!)
- The Golden Key. Will it help? - That's good.
It'll be incredible if we can switch places.
(Golden Key)
It'll be amazing.
- Let's switch places. - Sounds good.
- Dream all you want. - Let's switch places.
- Do well until the end. - Avalokitesvara Bodhisattva.
(What kind of Golden Key will the lucky member, Ji Hyo get?)
It'll be nice to switch places.
Let's switch places.
(Nervous)
That'll never happen.
- Please. - What is it?
- What? - Dimensional travel? What?
We got it for real.
(They get Dimensional Travel for real!)
(What?)
We got it for real.
What?
- We got it for real. - Seriously.
(They move to the gukbap place that was out of reach!)
Hey.
Who knew there was that option?
(Switch places with the other team. Swap the game pieces.)
- Ji Yu. - My goodness.
(Their devotion has been rewarded.)
- I got goosebumps. - My goodness.
This is insane.
(Their comeback is absolutely insane.)
- Everyone, I know... - This makes no sense.
- that it looks staged. - This makes no sense.
- I know that it looks staged. - This makes no sense.
(Out of nowhere)
- My goodness. - But I swear...
- that this isn't staged. - How did this happen?
Viewers will think that we've staged this.
(He can't believe his eyes.)
Our Buddhist faith won.
- This is just wrong. - I can't believe it.
(Upset)
I'm hungry.
- Our Buddhist faith won. - We won.
Our Buddhist faith won.
He goes to church.
- I didn't know... - He goes to church.
- He needs to stop lying. - that this was an option.
(Goosebumps)
I thought...
- No way. - As soon as you said it...
All right, everyone.
- Please clap. - How did this happen?
Please clap.
- How did this happen? - Here.
(With their Buddhist faith, they land on the gukbap square!)
- We're here. - Okay.
(Upset)
You know,
- we can pick one this time. - Yes.
- Put it back. - Why?
Team Jong Kook and Team Jae Seok switched places.
Team Jae Seok landed on the Golden Key square,
so they can have a draw.
The Golden Key gets reset each time.
All right. They won't get the same option again.
(They need to draw something big to win back their gukbap.)
I hope they get asked to write their names with their butts.
- Jae Seok. - Hey,
don't study them too closely.
I won't.
(Sensitive)
The one we picked might be wrinkly.
- Hey, hold them. - Look at those eyes.
You got the prosecutor's eyes again.
- Prosecutor. - Be careful not to show...
(Shuffling thoroughly)
- any wrinkles. - You should pick one.
Hey, wrinkle all of them.
- You should pick one. - Me?
I'm not so lucky when it comes to a draw.
- Shall I pick one? - That'll be better.
Jae Seok, we have Ye Eun.
- I'm unlucky. - Ye Eun.
(Ye Eun, who is lucky today, will draw a slip.)
- I'm unlucky. - Ye Eun, give it a go.
- Seriously. - Don't resent me.
(Even if I draw a bad one)
- Okay. - We won't resent you.
- Close your eyes and pick. - Ye Eun.
Ye Eun, go ahead.
(Even blocking her view)
- Give it a go. - You can tell the difference.
Advancing six squares won't be bad either, Ye Eun.
(Ye Eun will decide if they get to have lunch or not.)
Okay. We picked one.
- I have a good feeling about this. - Let's go.
- I think it's a bad one. - Ye Eun.
(Very sensitive)
- Isn't it a bit wrinkled? - Advancing six squares...
won't be bad either.
(The one who has been lucky, Ye Eun, picked the Golden Key.)
(Will it get them their gukbap back?)
- What? - What's this?
(Dimensional Travel)
No way.
(Dimensional Travel again?)
(You will switch places with your opposing team.)
- We got it! - No way!
(How is this possible?)
I picked it again. I did it for real.
(Against all odds, Ye Eun got them back on the gukbap square!)
Ye Eun!
I'm on a roll today!
How did this happen?
- You're incredible. - I'm on a roll today.
(The tables keep turning, stirring up a chaos!)
- It happened for real. - I'm on a roll today.
- It can't be helped. - I did it for real.
(Team Jong Kook has the chance to draw another Golden Key.)
- Pick one again. - It wasn't staged.
- Pick one again. - We'll pick it again. Put it back.
- We'll pick it again. Put it back. - Yes.
- This is incredible. - Seriously, I...
Seriously, I picked one blindly.
(Her luck is on a roll today.)
- You know that. - That's right.
You picked one at random.
- I... - Buddha...
really is fair. Even to a Christian,
- I'm a Christian. - he showed mercy.
(He showed mercy to a Christian too!)
- No way. - She is a devout Christian.
- Yes. - How did she pick it again?
That's how Buddha is.
Seriously, I got goosebumps.
I got goosebumps.
It was a statistical miracle.
That dampened...
(Their joy from earlier is totally crushed.)
- the team's spirit. - It just doesn't make any sense.
- Seriously, - I know it doesn't make any sense.
my Buddhist name is Wolgwang.
- I even had a Buddhist name. - Listen.
(Mr. Wolgwang appeals his Buddhist faith.)
- You should pick one. - You don't act like you do.
- "Moonlight Sonata." - You should pick one.
- You don't act like you do. - You know...
Does Wolgwang mean moonlight makes you crazy?
- Wolgwang. - You can do it.
(Unfortunately, the sun shines on him instead of the moon.)
Mr. Wolgwang.
- Please help us. - Now...
(Will Mr. Wolgwang do well under the sun?)
- If you're exhausted... - Good luck.
- We're set. - Mr. Wolgwang.
(He makes the fateful decision.)
- All right. Okay. - If you get it, we'll admit defeat.
- Seriously. We'll admit defeat. - Go.
- Dimensional Travel. - What? I have...
- a good feeling about. - It won't be that one.
- You won't pick it again. - You won't pick it again.
I think it's a new one.
- What? Hold on. - What could it be?
- Please. - Is it that one?
Wolgwang Jong Kook.
(Which Golden Key did Wolgwang draw?)
Please.
- Roll the Die Again. - Again.
(Roll the Die Again)
- Again? That's good. - Again?
(Golden Key: Roll the Die Again)
- That's good. - Not bad.
(It's not bad!)
That's good.
- Jong Kook, well done. - That means we'll eat.
(Luck continues! Roll the die again and move forward accordingly.)
- Not bad. - That means we'll eat.
(If Jong Kook rolls a 4,)
- Get four. - Four.
- Then we'll eat together. - Not bad.
(they can eat together!)
- All right. Four. - We'll root for you guys.
- Wait. - Is this the Buddha's plan?
- Four. - Does he want us to eat together?
(Did Buddha wish for a harmonious ending?)
How cool!
- Buddha! - Let's go.
(Hands up for Buddha)
- Four will be nice. - It's his plan.
(Team Jong Kook: 2. Temple food, 4. Gukbap)
- Two or four. - Two, three, or four will be nice.
- Four. - You're at the temple.
You're at the temple, so you'll get four.
- Two or four. - Okay.
(Dark intention)
I hope they get six and go to the Deserted Island.
(Giggling)
- Let's go and eat. - If you get four,
- it'll be a festival. - I'll let go of my greed.
- We can be happy together. - We'll be united.
(Even though let go of her greed, she makes a bow nonetheless.)
- Go. - All right.
- It'll be a drama. - The possibilities...
(The last roll of the die will determine their fate!)
- It'll be insane if she gets four. - It'll be a drama.
(Will the Buddha's blessing be with them this time as well?)
- The possibilities... - It'll be a drama.
- Go. - It'll be insane if she gets four.
- Six. - Six?
- It's the Deserted Island. - The Deserted Island.
(The final result, 6 will take them to...)
(the Deserted Island.)
- It's the Deserted Island. - This makes no sense.
- The Deserted Island. - Stop it.
(Read the room.)
- Gosh, Buddha. - The Deserted Island.
(Trying his best to hold back his laugh)
You don't need to grant everyone's wish.
(Buddha's betrayal)
- Oh, no. - We...
(A bitter ending for Mr. Wolgwang, who couldn't get the moonlight)
- All right. - This makes no sense.
- Can we go to the gukbap place? - Yes.
(Rubbing it in)
- Buddha... - Take care.
did this for fun.
- This is fun. - We'll get going.
(After a close match, only Team Jae Seok will get gukbap.)
- Okay. - Okay. Enjoy the food.
Let's not resent them.
How sad. Gukbap is my favorite food.
Sundaeguk sounds delicious.
- This is incredible. - The signs are insane.
(The signboards are so close yet so far.)
We're really hungry right now.
Team Jae Seok will get off and eat.
- Will they really stay here? - Will they sit here?
(Team Jong Kook will wait in the bus.)
- Will we sit here? - The place is cramped.
- Can't we smell the food? - Okay. That's good.
(Crying)
It's better to not smell it.
- We'll be back. - Enjoy the food.
- See you later. - We're sorry.
(Team Jae Seok gets off the bus.)
All right.
Even from here...
This alley is full...
- of old restaurants. - It smells like fermented skate.
(They enter an alley which smells good.)
- That's what's cool about Jongno. - It smells like doenjang stew.
When you step into the alley...
- that's surrounded by buildings... - This is incredible.
- This is the real deal. - It's bound to be delicious.
Jae Seok.
(He spots something.)
- This is the place. - No way.
- This is insane. - Is this the place?
(They find a sundaeguk place near the drop-off point.)
This is insane.
This place looks very good.
I can tell that they serve delicious food.
(We boil with care and sincerity.)
- This is insane. - Their food must be good.
(The sundaeguk place looks like they own the alley.)
This is amazing.
- Welcome. - May we eat in a corner?
(Asking for permission)
You can eat comfortably on the second floor.
(Employee)
Okay. The second floor.
- This is amazing. - Sundae.
(They smoothly get their permission to film!)
- Welcome. - Hello.
Hello.
This place is incredible.
They have julienned potato jeon.
(Right up the food fighter's alley)
It'll be tasty.
(Food Fighter is hungry after using up her luck.)
- Jae Seok. - Ye Eun.
Let's eat seafood jeon.
- Jae Seok. - If it weren't for you...
- If it weren't for you... - Seriously.
- Seriously. - They would've taken our spot.
- You're right about that. - Hello.
Come here.
- It's so cool. Jae Seok. - The smell is insane.
(They check out the menu as soon as they sit down.)
What's pork cheek sundae?
Jae Seok, blade-end fatback suyuk sounds delicious.
It looks so tasty.
- It looks so tasty. - It's their special dish.
Parboiled cuttlefish looks tasty too.
It looks so tasty.
(Swallowing)
There are so many tasty dishes.
- You know... - Jae Seok, let's order...
one julienned potato jeon and one suyuk.
- It'll be too much food. - It'll be too much food.
(Worried)
Sir,
which dishes are popular?
Sir, what should we eat?
Our signature dish is Gwanbuk sundaeguk.
(She recommends the signature sundaeguk.)
- Gwanbuk sundaeguk. - Yes.
- Then I'll order sundaeguk. - Suyuk sounds delicious.
- I'll get Gwanbuk sundaeguk. - Gwanbuk sundaeguk.
(He follows the recommendation without thinking twice.)
- Same here. - Three Gwanbuk sundaeguk.
I'll eat pork neck sundaeguk.
- Pork neck. - Can we order?
- Yes. - Suyuk is included.
Three Gwanbuk sundaeguk, one pork neck sundaeguk,
(Talking clearly)
and one julienned potato jeon.
(Unrestrained)
I'll have the sundaeguk set.
And...
(These foodies can't be satisfied with 1 sundaeguk per person.)
- Shall we order this? - It's a good choice.
We'll also get parboiled cuttlefish.
- Mixed. - Mixed parboiled cuttlefish.
Yes. We're set.
(They order a generous amount of food.)
Ye Eun, it's thanks to you...
It's thanks to Jae Seok...
- and Ye Eun that we're eating. - I know.
It's thanks to the two of you that we're eating.
- Are there spoons? - Weren't you on a diet?
I'm going to eat just a little bit of food.
(On a break from his diet)
I haven't even had breakfast. I'm hungry.
I'm so hungry. I'm going crazy.
Even the side dishes look nice.
(Gukbap's mate, kkakdugi, is looking good.)
They look neat.
Right? You can tell that this kimchi is tasty.
It looks like tasty kkakdugi.
(He puts a piece of kkakdugi in his mouth.)
(Impressed)
I'll eat it when I get the dishes.
(Kimchi gets his approval.)
It looks so tasty.
(There goes his diet.)
- Hey. - It looks so tasty.
This kkakdugi is tasty.
It looks so tasty.
(Suyuk is the first to be served.)
- It comes with the set. - It's mine.
- Please give me a piece. - Let us have a piece each.
- Come on. - Let us have a piece each.
Go ahead.
(Blade-end fatback suyuk has an amazing texture.)
We should've ordered it. Did we order it?
You get so much with the set.
- It's so... We should've gotten it. - This is incredible.
(What?)
Shall we order it?
(Blade-end fatback suyuk tastes insane on an empty stomach!)
Shall we do that?
(Surprised)
It's so tasty.
(His eyes go wide.)
(The perfect balance of meat and fat)
Why didn't you order the set?
Do you want it?
(Impressed)
It's so tender.
(My goodness)
- Eat it with kimchi. - It's so tasty.
- Is it tasty? - Is the food good?
- It's so good. - It's really tasty.
(Seok Jin and Jong Kook arrive at the restaurant.)
- Let's eat. Julienned potato jeon. - It's really tasty.
- Let's eat. - Let's eat.
- It's beyond tasty. - Congratulations.
All right.
(Why are they here?)
- Eat. - Scoot over.
It's insane.
- We'll pick two hungry members. - Okay.
(They played a quiz to pick two members for lunch.)
- Here comes the first question. - Okay.
What does "Sahara" mean...
in Sahara Desert?
- Sahara Desert? - It's harder...
- than I expected. - Let me answer.
- Demon. - Incorrect.
Let me answer. Sand.
- Incorrect. - Let me answer. Desert.
Correct.
Why did they name it Sahara Desert?
(Dumbfounded)
Who is the author of "The Tale of Hong Gil Dong,"
- the first Hangeul novel? - Let me answer.
- Gosh, I know the answer. - Heo Gyun.
- Correct. - Let's go. Okay.
(The two with the best common knowledge...)
Let's go.
- Okay. - The quiz was so easy.
(manage to escape!)
(Gukbap only allowed for the king of common knowledge)
I'll order pork neck sundaeguk too.
I'll order Gwanbuk sundaeguk.
- Okay. - Try it.
(Sharing suyuk)
- It's so tasty. - It's the blade-end fatback suyuk.
(Happy)
This suyuk is so tasty.
- Seok Jin's eyes look crazy. - It's the blade-end fatback, right?
(Humming)
Thank goodness Seok Jin made it here.
(This is it.)
- Blade-end fatback. - Hey.
This is insane. What's this?
(Once they're done with suyuk, the appetizer,)
Is there an option that just has meat?
(the main dish sundaeguk appears.)
- Yes, there is. - I'll get that.
- What's Gwanbuk? - It's pork neck sundaeguk.
(Boiling)
- Please give us more kimchi. - It has that ingredient.
Okay.
I'll add chili peppers.
(They add toppings that suit their tastes.)
This is incredible.
I feel bad for the others.
(Trying the soup first)
It can't be helped.
It's so tasty.
- Competitions can be ruthless. - That's right.
(He replenishes his energy spent on the die with spicy soup.)
I know. It can't be helped.
It's so tasty.
When you add chili peppers,
- it becomes spicy. - This is...
- It can't be helped. - The soup is insane.
- Competitions can be ruthless. - That's right.
(Sundae suits his taste.)
I know. It can't be helped.
What's this cuttlefish dish?
(Mixed cuttlefish complements sundaeguk.)
- What's this? - Mixed cuttlefish.
Mixed cuttlefish.
(Crunchy seafood and scallion jeon completes the party of textures.)
You know...
What's this?
(The taste makes him forget about his teammates.)
- Seafood and scallion jeon. - Try the jeon.
- It's good. - It's so tasty.
We... How is the food?
(An audience appears.)
- Haha. - Are you enjoying the food?
(The three siblings couldn't hold back their hunger.)
- It's so tasty. - It's so tasty.
- It's insane. - Really?
- Is it really good? - It's so tasty.
(Sticking out her tongue)
- What's up with you? - Earlier...
- My goodness. - Did you try it?
(He is at the end of his patience.)
Everything looks delicious.
(Smelling the food makes them want to cry.)
That jeon is insane.
(The unhappiest person in the world)
- Sundae. - It's so tasty.
- Ji Yu. - Yes?
Can you do pansori?
Pansori?
(Singing)
Oh, my
(Startled)
Sundaeguk is delicious
Let's eat sundaeguk together
Hey!
- She has the spirit. - How was it?
- Not bad. - Ari, arirang
- Seuri seurirang - My goodness.
- Ari, arirang, seuri seurirang - My goodness.
(This pansori singer has so much charisma.)
Arariga natne
(Singing passionately)
- What do you think? - It's so...
(Laughing so hard)
Arariga natne What do you think?
Stop it.
(Singing)
Sundaeguk is delicious
(The desperate cry of a hungry woman)
- She is good. - I know. She is good.
(Although she never learned pansori, she is good.)
Please tell us how it feels to be on the show through pansori.
(It's not enough.)
(My goodness)
You can sit down.
Oh, yes, this is great
Thank goodness I'm on Running Man
(The pansori machine sings passionately.)
(She did this much.)
- Give her food already. - Give her food.
(Very satisfied)
- Eat by yourself. - Give her food.
Eat by yourself.
(Feeling deflated)
- No, let's eat together. - No.
(She got a bit of food for the lunchtime gugak show.)
- No. - Eat by yourself.
She has the spirit.
The production crew should eat as well.
Let's eat together.
Come on. I'll pay for real.
(Thanks to Jae Seok, everyone fills their stomach!)
- All right. - Thank you for the food.
Don't mention it.
Do we need to roll the die twice?
(They continue to play Jongno Marble.)
Yes, roll the die twice.
Team Jong Kook needs to sit out for the Deserted Island.
(Team Jong Kook skips a turn...)
(since they're in the Deserted Island.)
- We need to roll the die twice. - You're right.
(Team Jae Seok needs to roll twice in a row.)
It'll be nice to get five.
(Team Jae Seok: 5. Golden Key, 6. Prize)
- Okay. - Five or six.
- Good luck. - Let's go.
- Don't move. - Five or six.
(Team Jae Seok wants a 5 or a 6.)
- It's okay. - Stay still, stay still!
(What did they roll?)
- Six! - Six!
(They rolled a 6!)
- Don't dodge it. - I knew it.
- You're the best! - This is amazing.
(They secured a prize ball.)
- It's really amazing. - Duksung Girls' High School?
I told you to stand still.
(The second roll of Team Jae Seok)
Let's go!
- Don't touch it. Stay still. - Stop.
- Five! - Two, three, four!
(The second roll is a 5!)
- Deserted Island. - Deserted Island. Congratulations!
(They landed on a Deserted Island for the first time.)
We won't be doing anything.
- Let's go. - Six.
(Next is Team Jong Kook's turn.)
- Three! - Three or five.
- Three! - Three!
(Team Jong Kook got a 2.)
- Two. - It's the penalty space!
(Their turn ends with a penalty ball.)
It's the penalty space.
- Haha. - Sir.
(Team Jae Seok pulls ahead thanks to unlucky Haha.)
How could you roll a two?
We'll go to Duksung Girls' High School, the first stop,
(They head to Duksung Girls' High School,)
and do a mission.
- When are we going to move? - We can do this!
(where Team Jae Seok landed.)
(Duksung Girls' High School: A school established...)
Duksung Girls' High School was established 100 years ago...
(around 100 years ago for women's education,)
(which had been oppressed)
to educate women who were oppressed.
- It's pretty. - Nice.
This mission is Speak With Your Actions...
with the citizens, where you'll be playing with the citizens.
(Min Se Yeon, Jeon Hee Eun, Kim Da Yeon)
Da Yeon and Hee Eun are determined. Let's do this!
(Un Nyun from "The Slave Hunters.")
(Clip-clop)
(Watch his mouth)
Are you making fun of my friend?
(A carbon copy of his rhombus-shaped mouth)
- Do it properly. - She's good.
(The Duksung student passes it on pretty well.)
That student is good.
(He has a cursed tongue, but will he be good with his body?)
She's good. The students are good.
He's ruining things.
(Hopping)
- He can't use his body at all. - Look at his lips.
(It turned into a lizard with a crooked mouth.)
His lips.
I'm so glad!
- Amazing. - Incorrect.
- Well, it's... - He's really bad at games.
- Are you blaming it on me again? - No!
Here's the keyword. Get ready.
(Next, Team Jong Kook plays.)
- Is it Ji Yu? - Come here.
Let's do this. Just do the exact same thing.
("Good job, Yeon Jin!" from "The Glory")
I didn't see it.
(Bringing Jang Mi Hee back)
Good.
She's good. Good job, Ji Yu!
(Perfect acting)
(I'll eat everything, except the gold teeth.)
She really came determined.
You're really bringing it out well.
Ji Yu is amazing.
(Compared to her acting skills,)
(she's not good at conveying the message.)
She's so funny.
"Even a worm will turn?" That's not correct, right?
Incorrect.
(All Team Jong Kook did was watch her acting show.)
So that's what it was.
- What is this? - Bye.
- Bye! - Bye! Thank you.
(The results of the mission with Duksung's students)
- All the best! - Thank you!
I hope you get into a good university!
Team Jae Seok won in the mission, so we'll give you two balls each.
(Team Jae Seok wins.)
(Team Jae Seok gets 2 name balls each.)
Okay!
- Team Jong Kook will roll it first. - They're...
(It's time to roll the die again.)
We can get anything except a six.
- One, two, or three. - Let's go.
Okay. I'll roll it.
(Team Jong Kook is far behind.)
- Let's go! - This is good.
- If it comes... - Make it fun!
- We can win! - We've gathered together!
(Back to the Deserted Island)
It's the Deserted Island.
- Three or six. - Let's do this. Three or six.
(Next is Team Jae Seok.)
Let's go! Three or six!
Please. Please let it be a 3 or a 6.
Three.
(Golden Key again!)
The Golden Key.
We're amazing!
(Penalty Black Hole)
Move to the nearest penalty space.
- Okay! - One space forward.
(They accumulate a penalty ball and move 1 square.)
- It's okay. - One space forward.
We can just win.
(With one last roll remaining, Team Jae Seok is still in the lead.)
We'll head to do the final mission.
- Okay! - It's really hot.
I hope we win.
(They head to a cafe near Bae Ryeom's House.)
I think we're going to win.
- I have a good feeling about this. - I think we're going to win.
- Team Jae Seok, you've come... - Yes?
- to Bae Ryeom's House in Gye-dong. - I see.
(Team Jae Seok's destination: Bae Ryeom's House)
- We came to a nearby cafe. - Nice.
It is a public hanok and historic house in Seoul,
believed to have been built in 1930.
It's a traditional urban hanok designed in a mieum-shape.
If it was built in 1930, it was built before the war.
There's a famous construction company here. The Gyedong building.
- It's right there. - There?
(Mr. Common Knowledge adds to the explanation.)
- Is it still there? - It's the one right there.
- Gyedong... - Jae Seok...
(He can't believe it.)
knows everything.
Let's roll the die.
(Time to roll the die)
The last roll. You should roll it, Jae Seok.
They're in the Deserted Island.
(Team Jae Seok can escape with one roll.)
We have a long way to finish.
We're almost there. We've come so far.
(Team Jong Kook can't escape even if they roll a 6.)
Right. Let's finish this.
Can't we get out?
(Backing out)
We can't. I won't roll the die anymore.
Do we have any chance of winning?
(For Team Jong Kook to win,)
- No. - If Team Jae Seok...
throws a 1 or 2,
(Team Jae Seok needs to roll small numbers consecutively.)
- That's right. - You get another chance.
If their die comes up low...
- Yes, - and ours comes up high,
That's right.
- Then we... - Three!
(A 3 will secure them a tablet.)
If you roll a three, we get a tablet computer.
- We need a 5 or a 6. - If their die comes up low...
(With a 5 or 6, they can escape at once.)
We can leave if we reach this point, right?
I think this is also fine.
(They could secure the tablets and escape in the next round!)
Yes. The tablet computer is fine.
- The best option is... - Three, five, or six.
(Team Jae Seok's goals are 3, 5, or 6.)
- Three, five, or six. - Three, five, or six.
We can finish with a 6 as well. It's 3, 5, or 6. A 50 percent chance.
(Team Jae Seok: 3. Tablet, 5 and 6. Escape)
Three, five, or six. Three, five, or six.
A 50 percent chance.
(3 out of 6)
- The tablet computer... - Three, five, or six!
(Going ahead of himself)
I won't give anyone the tablet computer.
Me too.
- I won't give it to anyone. - Three, five, or...
(Team Jae Seok can end the game with one roll.)
- six. - Six!
- Three, five, or six. - Three, five, or six.
(If Team Jae Seok rolls a 5 or a 6, Team Jong Kook loses.)
(Kiss)
- Three, five, or six! - One!
- One, one! - One, one!
(Team Jong Kook gets a chance if they roll a small number.)
You've been rolling threes all day.
(If they roll a 3, they secure a big prize.)
Yu Jae Seok, three!
(If they roll a 5 or a 6, they win right away.)
- Yu Jae Seok, three! - Let's finish it.
- Finishing it would be nice too. - Okay!
- Let's go. - Three, five, or six.
(He threw it.)
- One, two. - Three, five, or six.
- Let's go. Stop. - One or two. It's a one.
- Please! - It's okay. Stay still.
(Will they roll 1 of the 3?)
- One. - Two, two.
- One, one. - Let's go!
Seriously?
(They land on Pandora's Golden Key.)
- No! - It's over.
- It's a two. It's the Golden Key. - Golden Key.
- Golden Key. Okay. - Switch places.
(Dimensional Travel)
- I hope it's "switch places." - Switch places.
Let's switch places.
(If they get Dimensional Travel, they'll turn the table!)
We're getting the Golden Key even at the end.
We shouldn't get "swap pieces."
If they get "swap pieces," we win.
Double!
Pick the Golden Key.
- Ssaebssaeb! - Okay!
Okay!
- Go, go. - Go, go!
Go, go!
(He picked it!)
(Getting possessed)
(Having a shamanic ritual to get "Dimensional Travel.")
Please!
(Whose wish will the dice deity grant?)
- Go down! - Go down!
Please!
(Glance)
(Kong also saw it.)
Go down!
Please!
Hold on.
(No way.)
Is it "switch places?"
We're doomed!
He doesn't look happy!
(Which Golden Key did Se Chan draw?)
- We're... - They're doomed!
(Dimensional Travel)
(They really got "Dimensional Travel.")
(They were lucky!)
Really?
(Hitting)
Seriously.
(We're in trouble.)
- Really? - What is this?
- Okay! - Let's switch!
(Team Jae Seok and Team Jong Kook switch places.)
Let's go!
Does this even make sense?
We can roll and finish now!
(Start)
- We can leave. - We can finish.
(If Team Jong Kook rolls a 3 or bigger, they escape.)
- We can finish. - We need a five.
- What is this? - Anything above four.
- Why did you pick that? - This is the worst!
This is the worst!
Of all things...
(Right before the final destination,)
Why did you pick that?
We've been doing so well.
(they handed the spot over to Team Jong Kook.)
This is unbelievable.
They have to pick a Golden Key.
(Team Jong Kook too)
Do we have to pick?
(Team Jong Kook can't avoid drawing the Golden Key.)
We should roll after picking one.
What if we get "Dimensional Travel" again?
Switch places!
(You don't know how it will end yet.)
- They might pick it again. - It gets picked so often.
I got goosebumps.
If Seok Sam picks "Dimensional Travel,"
(Hopeful)
Can I pick it? Would that be all right?
(Golden Key)
- Do it, Seok Sam. - I used up my luck.
- Do you want to pick, Ji Hyo? - No.
- You should pick, Ji Hyo. - You can pick.
Seok Sam should pick.
(Unlucky Hand)
- No. - It's the last time.
- No. He's unlucky. - From my perspective...
Right. I won't pick. Ji Hyo!
(Upset)
Do you want to do it or not?
- I want to try. - Right?
(Seok Sam loves to play "a crucial role.")
Let him try.
- Right. - You should do it if you want.
(Goodness)
Just say it confidently.
- Let me do it. - Just do it.
(He secures the crucial role.)
- I wouldn't be unlucky forever. - Right.
They're here. Go, Seok Jin.
- The last one. - Last one. "Dimensional Travel."
(Seok Sam volunteers himself to pick the Golden Key.)
- Okay! - Okay!
- Okay! - Let's go!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
My hands are cursed!
- Let's go! - I'll throw this.
The last one remaining!
(He picks the last card that he didn't touch.)
(Will it be another Dimensional Travel?)
Switch places!
Double Dice Chance!
(Double Dice Chance)
(You get an extra die. roll 2 dice to move.)
Double Dice Chance!
(A huge stroke of luck)
(Seok Sam played his role as a hero perfectly!)
- We won! - We won!
- We won! - We won.
(They got Double Dice Chance with 3 squares left to the goal!)
They need to get 1 and 1.
- We won! - We won!
(It's as if they've already won.)
- We won! - It's over.
(Deflated)
One and one.
- One and one. - One and one.
(Team Jong Kook will fail to finish if they get 1 and 1.)
- We won! - We won!
(Team Jae Seok did all the work for nothing.)
Let's throw them. We just need to avoid rolling a one.
(Team Jong Kook can roll two dice.)
- Of course, in the end... - In the end...
- Ji Yu should throw them. - Yes, Ji Yu.
(The Double Dice to decide their fates are in Ji Yu's hands!)
- Hold on. - Roll them, Ji Yu.
- The red one. - Let's do this.
- Just don't roll 1 and 1. - Yes. Anything except 1 and 1.
It would be the best if you roll double ones.
Double ones would be amazing.
Statistically, there's no way we'd roll two ones.
(Team Jong Kook went to all 3 Deserted Islands against all odds.)
One and one!
One, two,
(What about this time?)
- three! - One and one!
Step back!
Please, please.
- One. - What?
(What about the other one?)
What?
- One and one! - One and one!
Yes!
(It's a 3!)
(They succeed in finishing by rolling a total of 4!)
It's a relief.
(That was a close one.)
We barely made it.
(Team Jong Kook's dice gave them a scare until the end.)
- We barely made it. - My heart is racing.
- We won. - And the final result...
(Team Jong Kook)
Team Jong Kook made it all the way around Jongno Marble!
We made it out!
We won.
(Team Jong Kook made it all the way around Jongno Marble.)
I was so shocked when you rolled a one.
Well done.
(They overcame 3 Deserted Islands and turned the tables.)
We barely made it.
If you got 1 and 1...
(What a pity.)
Things were going so well.
We lost it all in just one move.
We were sinning the whole time,
(Suddenly speaking clearly)
- only to get turned around. - Right. At the last second.
- I know. - This is nice.
This is really disappointing.
(Team Jae Seok was leading,)
It's so disappointing.
- We were winning the whole time. - Seriously.
(but they gave away the win at the last moment.)
I can't believe we won.
(A blessing in disguise)
I almost gave up.
We pulled off a comeback!
(Excited)
It was an unbelievable comeback.
So Team Kim Jong Kook is the winner.
(Team Jong Kook wins Jongno Marble.)
- Okay! - Yes!
- We won? - We won!
- That was so close. - You know what?
We had all the good stuff.
(Doing mental gymnastics)
This is a refreshing victory.
- This is too bad. - It was so close.
Today's Jongno tour was prepared...
(The hidden meaning behind today's race)
to celebrate our 815th episode...
- and the upcoming Liberation Day. - I see.
The S telecommunication company's AI model, A.X K2, analyzed...
(With its unique AI technology)
18,776 independence activists to recreate their stories...
and set up ten meaningful paths nationwide.
And the paths are called...
the 18,776 Independence Activists Remembrance Trail.
The spaces you landed on today...
(The places they went to were part of the trail.)
are part of those trails.
They are Remembering the Women Who Led Independence...
and Remembering Independence Built on Education.
(Remembering the Women Who Led Independence)
(Remembering Independence Built on Education)
If you connect the spaces marked on the game board,
(Today's Jongno Marble followed the trail...)
it will complete...
(of independence activists.)
the actual historic trails.
So, the spots we visited today have a deep meaning.
We carried out the missions along those trails.
With Team Kim Jong Kook's victory,
we will now reveal the prizes and penalties for today.
But before that,
Team Kim Jong Kook never landed on prize spaces today.
- They didn't? - No.
- Then what? It's just meaningless? - Is it meaningless?
(They skipped all the prize spaces.)
Is it a dud?
So, Team Kim Jong Kook is not getting any prizes.
(With 0 accumulated prize,)
(they fail to win any prize.)
- It's okay. - Yes!
- Avoiding penalties is enough. - That's what matters.
(Positive thinking)
- We avoid the penalties. - That's the prize.
It's as good as a prize.
- This is really... - Serves you right!
- That's too bad. - Okay.
- Now, we will reveal the penalties. - Okay. Penalties.
(Time to reveal 3 penalties for Team Jae Seok)
What are the penalties?
- Reveal them from the bottom up. - Open it.
- Sophora root tea? My goodness. - Sophora root tea.
(Yuck)
- Sophora root tea? - Sophora root tea.
This is the worst.
What is it?
- Water slap. - Water slap.
(The final penalty)
- Here. - Water slap.
- Water bucket. - Water bucket.
Why does it all have to be water?
(Penalty: Water bucket)
- This is the worst. - It's horrible.
So Team Yu Jae Seok will get three penalties.
Water slap, sophora root tea, and water bucket.
These are the three penalties you are receiving.
We receive all those penalties?
(For each penalty, the 2 people whose names are drawn...)
- All of us? - You get all of them.
(will carry out the penalty.)
- All three of them? - Yes.
If my name is not drawn,
(They added the name balls into the penalty box themselves.)
- I can avoid the penalty, right? - Then you don't have to do it.
I'm so nervous.
We can write down the names we want.
(Team Jae Seok agreed to put their own names in the prize box.)
(Endless betrayals ended up packing their penalty box to the brim.)
I put it in here earlier. What was that?
(And finally...)
But we're going to win.
- All right. First... - Please.
(Ye eun, 8, Jae Seok, 7, Se Chan, 7, Jin Ho, 6)
Let's start with the water slap.
(They have similar numbers of penalty balls.)
- Water slap. - Water slap.
(First penalty: Water slap)
Water slap.
- Two people. - Two people?
(They'll draw 2 penalty balls to decide who to take the penalty.)
- Please... - It was so close at the end.
- Please. - Seriously...
I'll pick one person first.
(Which 2 people will get the simple-but-annoying water slap?)
- I'm unlucky at times like this. - Penalty.
- Water slap. - Water slap.
This is for the water slap.
- Yu Jae Seok. - It's Se Chan.
- Water slap. - It's okay.
(Se Chan)
- This is better. - Water slap.
- Water slap is better. - You might get picked again.
Are we putting the balls back in the box?
(The drawn ball goes back into the box.)
Yes. We will put them back in.
- We're putting them back in? - They're going back in.
We're putting them back in?
It will be funny if Se Chan keeps getting picked.
Okay.
(Who is Se Chan's water-slap partner?)
It will be funny if Se Chan keeps getting picked.
- Yu Jae Seok. - Yu Jae Seok.
(Penalty 1. Water Slap: Jae Seok and Se Chan)
Come here.
Give me that.
(Jin Ho and Ye Eun passes the first penalty.)
- All right. - This is insane.
I'll do it right away. Please stay focused.
(They get to water slapping right away.)
- Okay. - Water slap.
- I'll go first. - Okay.
One, two, three.
(Splashing)
Three.
(Sputtering)
(The baby octopus and the monkfish wash each other's face nicely.)
- It's done. - It's refreshing!
That looks cool and refreshing.
- It looks so cool. - All right then.
(Water slap completed)
- Next. - Next.
(Next penalty is sophora root tea.)
It's sophora root tea.
Sophora root tea.
(Whose name will he draw?)
- This is sophora root tea. - You two should do it.
- Yang Se Chan. - You two can continue.
- Yu Jae Seok. - Yu Jae Seok.
(Yu Jae Seok)
(He drew his own name 2 times in a row.)
All right. Let's go!
Again...
(His goal)
- Yang Se Chan. - What?
It will be funny if you draw Se Chan's name again.
(Who will be enjoying sophora root tea with Jae Seok?)
It will be funny.
- What? - Who is it?
- Hong Jin Ho. - Hong Jin Ho.
- Oh, no. - Hong Jin Ho.
- The handwriting... - All right.
(Penalty 2. Sophora root tea: Jae Seok and Jin Ho)
- Ye Eun's name isn't in here. - All right.
- Ye Eun's name isn't in here. - I just want to avoid the bucket.
(Ddochi who has the most name balls avoided the penalty again.)
My name is in here. I have two balls in here.
Is this the sophora root tea?
It's fine as long as I avoid the water bucket.
I just want to avoid the water bucket.
Drink it up.
This is really bitter.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
(Cheers)
Bottoms up.
- This is bad. - It's really bitter.
(It looks like beer, but it tastes horrible.)
On such a hot day.
I just can't drink it.
- Me neither. It's too bitter. - I know.
(They drank up the sophora root tea.)
- It's so bitter. - It's really bitter.
(The sophora root tea is bitter until the next day.)
It's too bitter.
- You taste it for 3 to 4 hours. - Water bucket?
(In tatters)
Your tongue stays numb.
- Next up is the water bucket? - You taste it for 3 to 4 hours.
That is my least favorite.
- Water bucket is too tough. - Water bucket.
Darn it!
(The final penalty left is the water bucket.)
Next up is the water bucket.
- It's just too bitter. - Water bucket.
It's really bitter, but I can put up with it.
- I don't want the water bucket. - It's fine as long as you avoid it.
We have to pick someone else.
Please set it up.
- Oh, no. What do we do? - We have to avoid this one.
We pour water over our heads, right?
(Setting up the place for the douse of the water)
That's better.
I thought we'd throw water in our faces.
(It's the worst penalty because you'll go home soaked.)
There are so many balls in the penalty box.
How many balls do I have?
- I don't have many. - Draw the ball.
(Starting the draw for 2 to take the most dreaded penalty)
- Who will it be? - Se Chan?
(Jae Seok picked a ball.)
(Who is the unlucky first pick?)
- Who will it be? - Se Chan?
- I have too many balls in there. - Water bucket.
- Yang Se Chan! - Yang Se Chan!
(Yang Se Chan)
(Yang Se Chan is picked again.)
- It's Yang Se Chan. - Can I draw the ball?
Go ahead.
I have too many balls in the box.
- But... - You have a lot of balls.
You and I have many balls.
You do have so many balls.
- Pick Yu Jae Seok. - I don't have many.
Hey, if you pick me,
I get all three penalties.
It's okay.
- That's not bad. - All three penalties.
(Glancing)
- You can't look. - Don't look.
- I didn't look. - That's not bad.
(He tries to rig it.)
- You can't look. - Don't look.
Yu Jae Seok.
(Serious face)
You have to put it down first.
- I put it down. - Okay.
(His hand is empty.)
- I'll pick a ball now. - Just pick one.
(He starts his hunt.)
There you go.
With the bad luck on my hand today,
I'll probably end up drawing you.
Don't pick me.
- One, two, three. - Let's go.
(Who will be the final person to take the water splash?)
Yu Jae Seok.
(Yu Jae Seok)
(Yu Jae Seok gets all three penalties.)
(He has unbelievable luck!)
- All three penalties! - Jae Seok.
- Unbelievable. - I'm being unlucky today.
(Jae Seok gets water slap, sophora root tea, and water bucket.)
It's my unluckiest day.
- He's Unlucky Hand. - I hit the triple crown.
I got picked twice. You know that.
- Three and two. - This is my third penalty.
(They have nothing to say because they picked each other.)
- You can do that to each other. - You two have great chemistry.
The two Bucktooth Brothers have such a great bond.
Come here. I'll pour it over your head.
(Two Pouty Mouths meet again.)
Such a great bond.
- This is... - That's too much water.
- You pour water on each other. - It's a lot.
This is too much water.
(The water bucket has enough water for a half-body bath.)
I just heard him say, "This is too much water."
Can you believe it?
- All right. - All right.
(Baby Octopus gets ready for a shower first.)
One...
(Accepting it with humility)
- Pour it slowly. - It will be cool.
- Pour it. - So he can feel it.
Ssaebssaeb, throw it all at once.
(Just dump both of them over him.)
Pour it. It's okay.
(He's planning to pour his own water over Jae Seok.)
Hang on. Here I go.
- Just throw it. - Okay. One,
- two, three. - Slowly.
(A thorough wash)
(Picking it up)
He missed the timing.
(He's caught red-handed.)
He missed the moment.
It was too heavy. I was going to pour it, but...
- He missed the timing. - He was too late.
(Monkfish just ended up getting on Jae Seok's nerves.)
- This is what we wanted. - Be careful.
(He's going all-out.)
- Hold it tight. - Here I go.
- Okay. - All right.
(Thorough)
It's so refreshing!
- Oh, dear. - My goodness!
Stop it!
Why doesn't it end?
- Nice. - My goodness.
(The water splash ended right before he got gills.)
(All 3 penalties completed!)
That was so cool.
- It feels so cool. - You're the best.
- Good job. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - That was nice.
(A huge thanks to Hong Jin Ho and Kim Ji Yu for making us laugh)
- Listen. - You were so cool.
We had a lot of fun.
The temperature is expected to reach 37°C.
(Sweltering heat every day!)
I'm dripping with sweat.
It's so hot.
(The brutal real-world heat)
This is beautiful.
(A cave kingdom to blow away the heat)
- It's so cool in here. - I love it.
What is this place?
(There's another secret space hidden inside?)
- Are we entering a magical world? - Who are they?
- Hello. - Who are they?
(Here comes the fairy trio...)
- Hello. - Hello.
(in charge of this place.)
I want to fall in love.
(Fairy No. 1, straight to the point in her search for love)
- I want a good man. - You want to find someone.
(Unveiling the secret weapon...)
- She's so bad. - Why did she say...
she practiced the "Catch Catch" moves?
(that she's hidden all this time)
You were dancing "Gangnam Style."
(Brimming over with natural talent)
You're showing off so many different sides of you...
- after a long time. - Me?
- You are... - What kind of person are you?
(A fairy of a thousand faces, Lee Ju Yeon)
- Her skin is so pale. - You have such fair skin.
(Next to her, there's a shy, snow-white ice fairy.)
- You're supposed to dance. - Where?
(She's so clumsy when she's on a variety show.)
- You... - Se Chan and Haha.
(Stop treating me like a naive kid.)
You think you can act so high and mighty?
(Her full-on tomboy mode is on.)
Why is she back as a thug?
(Intimidated)
- I was enjoying my vacation. - Hello.
(A tomboyish ice fairy, Kim Ji Eun)
I'll sing with no music.
(A master singer who fills the cave without any backing tracks)
Can you sing live in a cave?
(A storm vocal fairy, Jung Eun Ji)
(True to her name)
I got goosebumps.
- Oh my. - What is this?
(The real goosebumps are getting started now.)
Someone's here!
- Oh my... - Gosh, this is really...
(Vacation Inferno versus Vacation Paradise)
It's driving me crazy.
(Their split fates await them.)
- There you go. - Hey, you. Come here.
- You're in for it. - Sorry.
(Who will break free from the curse of the sweltering heat?)
- My gosh. - Run!
- Run! - Oh, no!
- It's coming! - Let's run!
(Beat the Heat With a Scratch Vacation)
(Running Man)